[
  {
    "question": "She _________ to London last week.",
    "choices": [
      "go",
      "goes",
      "went",
      "is going"
    ],
    "answer": "went"
  },
  {
    "question": "In international trade, companies must __________ trade regulations.",
    "choices": [
      "comply with",
      "abide by",
      "follow",
      "adhere to"
    ],
    "answer": "comply with"
  },
  {
    "question": "The new employee _________ her job very well.",
    "choices": [
      "learn",
      "learns",
      "learned",
      "is learning"
    ],
    "answer": "is learning"
  },
  {
    "question": "Please _________ your completed evaluation form on the table beside the door.",
    "choices": [
      "write",
      "leave",
      "make",
      "consider"
    ],
    "answer": "leave"
  },
  {
    "question": "Arvid's latest game console, the Star 212, _________ resembles earlier models.",
    "choices": [
      "closely",
      "closer",
      "closeness",
      "closest"
    ],
    "answer": "closely"
  },
  {
    "question": "Using the bank's app, customers can instantly pay bills through _________ transfer.",
    "choices": [
      "various",
      "electronic",
      "patient",
      "eager"
    ],
    "answer": "electronic"
  },
  {
    "question": "Remember to bring a laptop with you for today's software training _________ at the Alten Conference Center.",
    "choices": [
      "meet",
      "met",
      "meets",
      "meeting"
    ],
    "answer": "meeting"
  },
  {
    "question": "Pacetti Furnaces offers discounts on installations _________ the summer months.",
    "choices": [
      "above",
      "during",
      "besides",
      "including"
    ],
    "answer": "during"
  },
  {
    "question": "Agents from Research Excellence Ltd. will be touring _________ offices next week.",
    "choices": [
      "us",
      "ourselves",
      "we",
      "our"
    ],
    "answer": "our"
  },
  {
    "question": "When Mr. Awetimbi entered the conference room, he _________ that the audiovisual equipment had not been delivered.",
    "choices": [
      "notices",
      "noticed",
      "noticing",
      "noticeable"
    ],
    "answer": "noticed"
  },
  {
    "question": "Drivers must use parking area B while parking area A is undergoing _________ .",
    "choices": [
      "support",
      "traffic",
      "vehicles",
      "repairs"
    ],
    "answer": "repairs"
  },
  {
    "question": " A newsletter is distributed to staff _________ to describe the company's accomplishments for that year.",
    "choices": [
      "commonly",
      "broadly",
      "annually",
      "searchingly"
    ],
    "answer": "annually"
  },
  {
    "question": " Enable notifications and _________ updates by selecting your preferred device settings.",
    "choices": [
      "automates",
      "automatically",
      "automation",
      "automatic"
    ],
    "answer": "automatic"
  },
  {
    "question": " New employees of Lopez Construction must take several courses, _________ a power tool safety course.",
    "choices": [
      "as if",
      "such as",
      "in case of",
      "even so"
    ],
    "answer": "such as"
  },
  {
    "question": " Some programmers remain at one company for several years, but _________ depart sooner for better-paying jobs at other firms.",
    "choices": [
      "theirs",
      "either",
      "which",
      "many"
    ],
    "answer": "many"
  },
  {
    "question": " According to Travelers magazine, people have grown increasingly interested in _________ their vacation time outdoors in recent years.",
    "choices": [
      "visiting",
      "spending",
      "charging",
      "closing"
    ],
    "answer": "spending"
  },
  {
    "question": " After interviewing five candidates for the sales position, the manager _________ the most experienced one.",
    "choices": [
      "choice",
      "chosen",
      "chose",
      "to choose"
    ],
    "answer": "chose"
  },
  {
    "question": " The City of Mayville's _________ job fair will feature representatives from a variety of local businesses.",
    "choices": [
      "extreme",
      "specific",
      "upcoming",
      "prevailing"
    ],
    "answer": "upcoming"
  },
  {
    "question": " The Kopple Building was in very poor _________ the renovation.",
    "choices": [
      "condition",
      "conditioned",
      "conditioner",
      "conditional"
    ],
    "answer": "condition"
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ Mr. Khat has just been promoted to management, we now have an open sales-associate position.",
    "choices": [
      "Upon",
      "Until",
      "Since",
      "Despite"
    ],
    "answer": "Since"
  },
  {
    "question": "Don's Café uses only local fruits and vegetables in its _________ prepared dishes.",
    "choices": [
      "carefully",
      "careful",
      "caring",
      "cared"
    ],
    "answer": "carefully"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sales of truck parts _________ approximately 45 percent to BTR Manufacturing's revenue last year.",
    "choices": [
      "gave",
      "applied",
      "contributed",
      "donated"
    ],
    "answer": "contributed"
  },
  {
    "question": "The _________ northbound Coastal Express train will be arriving on track 5.",
    "choices": [
      "delay",
      "delays",
      "delayed",
      "delaying"
    ],
    "answer": "delayed"
  }, 
  {
    "question": "The Shellville City Council acted _________ when it decided to convert an unused railway to a multipurpose trail.",
    "choices": [
      "wisely",
      "entirely",
      "initially",
      "widely"
    ],
    "answer": "wisely"
  },
  {
    "question": "Overall _________ of museum archivists and curators is expected to grow steadily over the next ten years.",
    "choices": [
      "employee",
      "employment",
      "employed",
      "employable"
    ],
    "answer": "employment"
  },
  {
    "question": "With her _________ experience in graphic design, Ms. Abebe appears to be a suitable candidate for the book designer position.",
    "choices": [
      "vast",
      "plausible",
      "relieved",
      "conscious"
    ],
    "answer": "vast"
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ a Boskin electrical product is modified by the customer, the warranty is no longer valid.",
    "choices": [
      "Except",
      "So",
      "That",
      "If"
    ],
    "answer": "If"
  },
  {
    "question": "Retail sales of Kent Menswear collared dress shirts increase dramatically every October, _________ the brand's autumn sale.",
    "choices": [
      "so that",
      "due to",
      "therefore",
      "whereas"
    ],
    "answer": "due to"
  },
  {
    "question": "For security purposes, only authorized personnel of Jeffers Mines Ltd. may proceed _________ this checkpoint.",
    "choices": [
      "beyond",
      "without",
      "about",
      "between"
    ],
    "answer": "beyond"
  },
  {
    "question": "Heron Stationers _________ new business cards by the end of the week.",
    "choices": [
      "to order",
      "had been ordered",
      "will be ordering",
      "ordering"
    ],
    "answer": "will be ordering"
  },
  {
    "question": "At Key Beach Fashions, customers can check the _________ of their orders online.",
    "choices": [
      "reason",
      "agenda",
      "status",
      "intent"
    ],
    "answer": "status"
  },  
  {
    "question": "A prize will be awarded to _________ sells the most raffle tickets for the annual charity fund-raiser.",
    "choices": [
      "anybody",
      "yourselves",
      "everyone",
      "whoever"
    ],
    "answer": "whoever"
  }, 
  {
    "question": "The greenhouse temperature must remain _________ the specified range for plants to grow properly.",
    "choices": [
      "within",
      "because of",
      "as long as",
      "after all"
    ],
    "answer": "within"
  },
  {
    "question": "Please send a copy of _________ résumé to the hiring committee.",
    "choices": [
      "you",
      "yours",
      "yourself",
      "your"
    ],
    "answer": "your"
  },
  {
    "question": "Gnome Bicycle’s employee turnover rate has been quite steady _________ the past year.",
    "choices": [
      "toward",
      "over",
      "rather",
      "if"
    ],
    "answer": "over"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mainer Soft, Inc., offers a selection of video games, which are only _________ through its Web site.",
    "choices": [
      "sale",
      "sell",
      "sold",
      "sells"
    ],
    "answer": "sold"
  },
  {
    "question": "Changes to the travel reimbursement process will be explained at this month's staff _________ .",
    "choices": [
      "level",
      "schedule",
      "proposal",
      "meeting"
    ],
    "answer": "meeting"
  },
  {
    "question": "Stillman Canning creates stews and soups using а _________ family recipe.",
    "choices": [
      "trust",
      "trusted",
      "trusts",
      "trusting"
    ],
    "answer": "trusted"
  },
  {
    "question": "In its first week _________ operation, Sabon Hairstyling Salon had about 150 customers.",
    "choices": [
      "of",
      "to",
      "as",
      "by"
    ],
    "answer": "of"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ekari Industries is proud to announce its _________ merger with Bogin Enterprises.",
    "choices": [
      "whole",
      "external",
      "upcoming",
      "serious"
    ],
    "answer": "upcoming"
  },
  {
    "question": "All letters and packages are shipped in locked containers to ensure safe _________ .",
    "choices": [
      "deliver",
      "delivers",
      "delivered",
      "delivery"
    ],
    "answer": "delivery"
  },
  {
    "question": "This year, _________ three million passengers across China boarded domestic flights the day before the holiday weekend.",
    "choices": [
      "almost",
      "often",
      "more",
      "far"
    ],
    "answer": "almost"
  },
  {
    "question": "By the end of the workshop, participants will have a _________ understanding of how to request financial aid.",
    "choices": [
      "hard",
      "full",
      "best",
      "busy"
    ],
    "answer": "full"
  },  
  {
    "question": "Removing personal items from the floor of your workstation will _________ facilitate tomorrow's carpet cleaning.",
    "choices": [
      "greatness",
      "greats",
      "great",
      "greatly"
    ],
    "answer": "greatly"
  },
  {
    "question": "Audience members are asked to resist looking at their phones because presenters find it _________ .",
    "choices": [
      "distraction",
      "distract",
      "distractible",
      "distracting"
    ],
    "answer": "distracting"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hospital officials met with the architects _________ received an overview of the design of the new maternity center.",
    "choices": [
      "either",
      "instead",
      "or",
      "and"
    ],
    "answer": "and"
  },
  {
    "question": "Anyone planning to _________ for a pharmacy degree program should consider gaining laboratory work experience.",
    "choices": [
      "require",
      "vote",
      "apply",
      "complete"
    ],
    "answer": "apply"
  },
  {
    "question": "Even first-time Pictafix subscribers can use the software to create photo collages nearly _________ .",
    "choices": [
      "increasingly",
      "effortlessly",
      "recently",
      "especially"
    ],
    "answer": "effortlessly"
  },
  {
    "question": "The company's production issues were further _________ by an unexpected power outage.",
    "choices": [
      "complicate",
      "complicated",
      "complication",
      "complicating"
    ],
    "answer": "complicated"
  },
  {
    "question": "The board of directors at Ginishi Estate Investments is awaiting shareholder approval _________ acquiring more properties.",
    "choices": [
      "because",
      "providing",
      "before",
      "though"
    ],
    "answer": "before"
  },  
  {
    "question": "_________ assistant will be in the office today, but they can be contacted by e-mail.",
    "choices": [
      "Many",
      "Other",
      "Neither",
      "None"
    ],
    "answer": "Neither"
  },
  {
    "question": "Brynextech now has manufacturing _________ on both the east and west coasts.",
    "choices": [
      "facilities",
      "selections",
      "performances",
      "revisions"
    ],
    "answer": "facilities"
  },
  {
    "question": "Cowan Company is usually filled with the sound of people talking _________ in its research library.",
    "choices": [
      "during",
      "despite",
      "among",
      "except"
    ],
    "answer": "except"
  },
  {
    "question": "To predict erosion, geologists _________ the water absorption rate of soil near the mountain range.",
    "choices": [
      "monitor",
      "practice",
      "surround",
      "occupy"
    ],
    "answer": "monitor"
  },
  {
    "question": "Returns of merchandise with original tags and receipts are _________ accepted for up to 30 days after purchase.",
    "choices": [
      "general",
      "generally",
      "generalize",
      "generalized"
    ],
    "answer": "generally"
  },
  {
    "question": "The visiting delegation will join the CEO for refreshments after they finish the factory _________ .",
    "choices": [
      "toured",
      "tourism",
      "tourist",
      "tour"
    ],
    "answer": "tour"
  },
  {
    "question": "Cost should not be the only factor taken into account _________ choosing a contractor for a renovation.",
    "choices": [
      "back to",
      "when",
      "between",
      "in part"
    ],
    "answer": "when"
  },
  {
    "question": "We could reserve the auditorium; _________, we could consider meeting in one of the larger conference rooms.",
    "choices": [
      "alternatively",
      "immediately",
      "in particular",
      "such as"
    ],
    "answer": "alternatively"
  },
  {
    "question": "By requiring the _________ inspection of all assembly-line machines, the new policy will help improve workplace safety.",
    "choices": [
      "periodic",
      "period",
      "periodically",
      "periods"
    ],
    "answer": "periodic"
  },
  {
    "question": "The company, which Mr. Sato initially operated out of his own home, was _________ sold for several billion yen.",
    "choices": [
      "tightly",
      "subsequently",
      "severely",
      "evenly"
    ],
    "answer": "subsequently"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the interest of _________, product designer Yu Cai will remain the team lead until the project is completed.",
    "choices": [
      "continue",
      "continuity",
      "continuous",
      "continuously"
    ],
    "answer": "continuity"
  },
  {
    "question": "Owing to their _________ of hot, dry climates, evergreens like the Arizona cypress grow well in drought-prone areas.",
    "choices": [
      "tolerance",
      "abundance",
      "performance",
      "allowance"
    ],
    "answer": "tolerance"
  },
  {
    "question": "Alvin Parno's insightful column about the crisis in the international trade situation is very _________ .",
    "choices": [
      "attractive",
      "comfortable",
      "informative",
      "wealthy"
    ],
    "answer": "informative"
  },
  {
    "question": "Starlight Noodle House _________ to open its first North American restaurant early next year.",
    "choices": [
      "plan",
      "plans",
      "planner",
      "planning"
    ],
    "answer": "plans"
  },
  {
    "question": "For a small fee, Marvin's Fine Furniture will _________ items to customers' homes within two days of purchase.",
    "choices": [
      "deliver",
      "sell",
      "report",
      "spend"
    ],
    "answer": "deliver"
  },
  {
    "question": "There is no price _________ among Kalteco's three refrigerator models.",
    "choices": [
      "differ",
      "different",
      "difference",
      "differently"
    ],
    "answer": "difference"
  },
  {
    "question": "McAlvey's Rental will provide the tents and seating needed _________ the upcoming festival.",
    "choices": [
      "against",
      "near",
      "into",
      "for"
    ],
    "answer": "for"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mr. Sorva handles all purchase orders _________ unless special approvals are needed.",
    "choices": [
      "he",
      "him",
      "his",
      "himself"
    ],
    "answer": "himself"
  },
  {
    "question": "We appreciate your patience _________ our technology team works to restore the connection.",
    "choices": [
      "if",
      "while",
      "whether",
      "but"
    ],
    "answer": "while"
  },
  {
    "question": "Davison Avionics' sales department is _________ recruiting additional team members.",
    "choices": [
      "actively",
      "active",
      "activate",
      "activity"
    ],
    "answer": "actively"
  },
  {
    "question": "It has been six months _________ Mr. Payne became president of Thornton Machinery.",
    "choices": [
      "since",
      "from",
      "where",
      "between"
    ],
    "answer": "since"
  },
  {
    "question": "The company has stayed profitable _________ by keeping operating costs low.",
    "choices": [
      "shortly",
      "highly",
      "mainly",
      "greatly"
    ],
    "answer": "mainly"
  },
  {
    "question": "Clients of Elise Salon receive text messages asking them to confirm their _________ .",
    "choices": [
      "appoint",
      "appointed",
      "appointing",
      "appointments"
    ],
    "answer": "appointments"
  },
  {
    "question": "According to a Consumer Now poll, Bricktown Realty provides the _________ efficient real estate services in the area.",
    "choices": [
      "very",
      "such",
      "quite",
      "most"
    ],
    "answer": "most"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tolle Accounting's employee manual states that constructive disagreements are part of an _________ office culture.",
    "choices": [
      "effect",
      "effects",
      "effective",
      "effectively"
    ],
    "answer": "effective"
  },
  {
    "question": "Marketing team members may work from home _________ they have their manager's permission.",
    "choices": [
      "as long as",
      "as a result of",
      "depending on",
      "together with"
    ],
    "answer": "as long as"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Petsonk Group is _________ to providing outstanding insurance at an affordable cost.",
    "choices": [
      "reminded",
      "accepted",
      "required",
      "committed"
    ],
    "answer": "committed"
  },
  {
    "question": "The board of directors decided last night that Tina Chau should _________ as head of the legal department.",
    "choices": [
      "continuous",
      "continue",
      "continued",
      "continuously"
    ],
    "answer": "continue"
  },
  {
    "question": "A large collection of bird fossils will be on display at the museum from May 15 _________ July 31.",
    "choices": [
      "during",
      "until",
      "around",
      "throughout"
    ],
    "answer": "until"
  },
  {
    "question": "Because so many members of the editorial staff use the printer, the office manager _________ has to order extra paper.",
    "choices": [
      "frequency",
      "frequent",
      "frequenting",
      "frequently"
    ],
    "answer": "frequently"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mr. Rhee thinks that the missing file is _________ in the archives.",
    "choices": [
      "locating",
      "somewhere",
      "removed",
      "especially"
    ],
    "answer": "somewhere"
  },
  {
    "question": "Halle Theft Protection notifies customers immediately whenever there is a _________ of data security.",
    "choices": [
      "breach",
      "contract",
      "secret",
      "reminder"
    ],
    "answer": "breach"
  },
  {
    "question": "The assembly instructions for the desk must be written very _________ to ensure that customers understand them.",
    "choices": [
      "clearer",
      "clearest",
      "clears",
      "clearly"
    ],
    "answer": "clearly"
  },
  {
    "question": "According to the Baker Financial Journal, investors' _________ for technology stocks rose sharply this quarter.",
    "choices": [
      "enthusiasm",
      "enthusiast",
      "enthusiastic",
      "enthusiastically"
    ],
    "answer": "enthusiasm"
  },
  {
    "question": "All outerwear made by Arctic Hare is designed to withstand _________ cold temperatures.",
    "choices": [
      "generously",
      "famously",
      "extremely",
      "suspiciously"
    ],
    "answer": "extremely"
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ scheduling an examination at Central Wellness Clinic, clients will be asked a few health-related questions.",
    "choices": [
      "Whereas",
      "When",
      "Although",
      "At"
    ],
    "answer": "When"
  },
  {
    "question": "Owing to staff relocations, the company now has a _________ of office space at its headquarters.",
    "choices": [
      "rate",
      "surplus",
      "factor",
      "profit"
    ],
    "answer": "surplus"
  },
  {
    "question": "Having participated in _________ interviews during her job search, Ms. McKray expects that she will be hired soon.",
    "choices": [
      "sizable",
      "countless",
      "plentiful",
      "much"
    ],
    "answer": "countless"
  },
  {
    "question": "Two prototypes of Viesso's mountain bike underwent user testing, and _________ were found to perform exceptionally well.",
    "choices": [
      "less",
      "whose",
      "which",
      "both"
    ],
    "answer": "both"
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ Ms. Uribe was promoted to director of development at Cranhurst International, she served in many other capacities.",
    "choices": [
      "Before",
      "Instead",
      "Likewise",
      "Consequently"
    ],
    "answer": "Before"
  },
  {
    "question": "Landscape designers usually present several renderings to clients to help them _________ the completed project.",
    "choices": [
      "appear",
      "resemble",
      "visualize",
      "express"
    ],
    "answer": "visualize"
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ silk will be imported from Japan for our evening-wear fashion designs next season.",
    "choices": [
      "Luxuriate",
      "Luxuriously",
      "Luxuries",
      "Luxurious"
    ],
    "answer": "Luxurious"
  },
  {
    "question": "If its advertising revenue declines further, the magazine's future prospects are _________ .",
    "choices": [
      "reported",
      "insignificant",
      "uncertain",
      "overlooked"
    ],
    "answer": "uncertain"
  },
  {
    "question": "The new microwave for the office kitchen should arrive _________ the week.",
    "choices": [
      "on",
      "along",
      "by",
      "within"
    ],
    "answer": "within"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mr. Samudio thanked the hotel staff for making _________ stay a comfortable one.",
    "choices": [
      "he",
      "his",
      "him",
      "himself"
    ],
    "answer": "his"
  },
  {
    "question": "The sales associates have been pleased with the new dress code _________ it was implemented last September.",
    "choices": [
      "here",
      "first",
      "since",
      "best"
    ],
    "answer": "since"
  },
  {
    "question": "At the beginning of the class, your instructor will inform you _________ additional materials are needed.",
    "choices": [
      "yet",
      "if",
      "however",
      "although"
    ],
    "answer": "if"
  },
  {
    "question": "Poole and Whitney Supply sells premier products for do-it-yourself home improvement _________ .",
    "choices": [
      "projects",
      "projection",
      "projecting",
      "projectors"
    ],
    "answer": "projects"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mouse pads _________ our redesigned company logo will be distributed after the workshop.",
    "choices": [
      "must display",
      "to be displayed",
      "displaying",
      "being displayed"
    ],
    "answer": "displaying"
  },
  {
    "question": "Employees who work part-time are not _________ for the company's profit-sharing plan.",
    "choices": [
      "famous",
      "admired",
      "reasonable",
      "eligible"
    ],
    "answer": "eligible"
  },
  {
    "question": "Brady Music Academy pairs students with qualified instructors _________ are professional wind and brass instrument players.",
    "choices": [
      "who",
      "when",
      "where",
      "whose"
    ],
    "answer": "who"
  },
  {
    "question": "Residents of Millier Street _________ city council members to approve the installation of a traffic light.",
    "choices": [
      "encouraged",
      "suggested",
      "argued",
      "reported"
    ],
    "answer": "encouraged"
  },
  {
    "question": "At the meeting tomorrow, Jing Huang, vice president of sales, will discuss the company's _________ to achieve its sales goals.",
    "choices": [
      "effortless",
      "efforts",
      "effortful",
      "effortlessly"
    ],
    "answer": "efforts"
  },
  {
    "question": "Chef Ferguson _________ mixed the spices during her cooking demonstration.",
    "choices": [
      "extremely",
      "expertly",
      "tightly",
      "finely"
    ],
    "answer": "expertly"
  },
  {
    "question": "To receive a parking pass, you must submit a _________ request to your supervisor.",
    "choices": [
      "formalize",
      "formally",
      "formality",
      "formal"
    ],
    "answer": "formal"
  },
  {
    "question": "The customer survey results show that there are _________ issues that need to be addressed.",
    "choices": [
      "faithful",
      "numerous",
      "classical",
      "rapid"
    ],
    "answer": "numerous"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ms. Liu requested that her mail be _________ to the New York office during the month of June.",
    "choices": [
      "forward",
      "forwards",
      "forwarded",
      "forwarding"
    ],
    "answer": "forwarded"
  },
  {
    "question": "Supeck Legal is closed while the sprinkler system is being replaced _________ the building.",
    "choices": [
      "into",
      "to",
      "throughout",
      "among"
    ],
    "answer": "throughout"
  },
  {
    "question": "Gabary Ltd. decided to expand its marketing staff, so salaries for newly hired employees are _________ high.",
    "choices": [
      "reasonably",
      "reasonable",
      "reasons",
      "reasoned"
    ],
    "answer": "reasonably"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ms. Baek needs to sign the standard _________ to start working as an operations consultant.",
    "choices": [
      "reference",
      "advice",
      "format",
      "agreement"
    ],
    "answer": "agreement"
  },
  {
    "question": "Companies relocating _________ headquarters to Burton County must submit a proposed timeline for the move.",
    "choices": [
      "them",
      "their",
      "themselves",
      "theirs"
    ],
    "answer": "their"
  },
  {
    "question": "Although a date has not been _________, the Culvert Silver Line is expected to resume operations next year.",
    "choices": [
      "positioned",
      "perfected",
      "specified",
      "amplified"
    ],
    "answer": "specified"
  },
  {
    "question": "Operating at a _________ of 100 sheets per minute, the Nobia XLR is one of the fastest photocopiers on the market.",
    "choices": [
      "period",
      "rate",
      "distance",
      "page"
    ],
    "answer": "rate"
  },
  {
    "question": "Dr. Cheon is _________ reluctant to accept new patients at this time given his current caseload.",
    "choices": [
      "understandably",
      "understandable",
      "understanding",
      "understood"
    ],
    "answer": "understandably"
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ customer will receive a free gift with any purchase at Trayton Tools on its opening day.",
    "choices": [
      "Certain",
      "All",
      "Few",
      "Each"
    ],
    "answer": "Each"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Elevpro jacket features an adjustable hood for extra _________ against cold weather.",
    "choices": [
      "protect",
      "protection",
      "protector",
      "protected"
    ],
    "answer": "protection"
  },
  {
    "question": "The reforestation plan is proceeding smoothly, although the organizers _________ some minor issues in the early stages.",
    "choices": [
      "concluded",
      "accomplished",
      "earned",
      "encountered"
    ],
    "answer": "encountered"
  },
  {
    "question": "The institute's directors have decided to reinvest the budget surplus _________ spending the extra money.",
    "choices": [
      "instead of",
      "paid for",
      "apart from",
      "offers to"
    ],
    "answer": "instead of"
  },
  {
    "question": "The clients could not agree on contract wording, and unfortunately, _________ could the lawyers.",
    "choices": [
      "perhaps",
      "meanwhile",
      "neither",
      "rather"
    ],
    "answer": "neither"
  },
  {
    "question": "References must be _________ by a human resources specialist before a job candidate arrives for an interview.",
    "choices": [
      "verifying",
      "verifies",
      "verified",
      "verification"
    ],
    "answer": "verified"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mr. Lee ended the department meeting _________ in order to greet a prominent client.",
    "choices": [
      "hardly",
      "widely",
      "immensely",
      "abruptly"
    ],
    "answer": "abruptly"
  },
  {
    "question": "The accounting software has been developed in an _________ fashion over the past two years.",
    "choices": [
      "increment",
      "incrementally",
      "increments",
      "incremental"
    ],
    "answer": "incremental"
  },
  {
    "question": "The document outlines possible _________ of building without a permit in the municipality.",
    "choices": [
      "adjustments",
      "consequences",
      "alignments",
      "designs"
    ],
    "answer": "consequences"
  },
  {
    "question": "While _________ are excited by the idea of relocation, the suggested timeline is problematic.",
    "choices": [
      "we",
      "our",
      "ours",
      "ourselves"
    ],
    "answer": "we"
  },
  {
    "question": "Work is underway to convert the vacant warehouse on Third Street _________ а restaurant.",
    "choices": [
      "than",
      "into",
      "as",
      "with"
    ],
    "answer": "into"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hossco has just announced the _________ annual revenues in company history.",
    "choices": [
      "high",
      "higher",
      "highly",
      "highest"
    ],
    "answer": "highest"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ms. Gellar and Mr. Carlton will manage the new social media department _________ .",
    "choices": [
      "doubly",
      "jointly",
      "variously",
      "considerably"
    ],
    "answer": "jointly"
  },
  {
    "question": "Processing time was increased because of an error on the permit _________ .",
    "choices": [
      "applying",
      "applicably",
      "applies",
      "application"
    ],
    "answer": "application"
  },
  {
    "question": "No submissions for the photography competition will be accepted _________ the June 20 deadline.",
    "choices": [
      "beyond",
      "since",
      "from",
      "once"
    ],
    "answer": "beyond"
  },
  {
    "question": "Researchers have found _________ high levels of pollution in a number of local ponds.",
    "choices": [
      "alarm",
      "alarmingly",
      "alarming",
      "alarmed"
    ],
    "answer": "alarmingly"
  },
  {
    "question": "The food that was provided for the conference on Saturday morning had actually been prepared the day _________ .",
    "choices": [
      "ago",
      "early",
      "before",
      "away"
    ],
    "answer": "before"
  },
  {
    "question": "For details about our language course offerings, or _________ in a class, please visit our Web site.",
    "choices": [
      "to enroll",
      "enrolled",
      "enrolls",
      "are enrolling"
    ],
    "answer": "to enroll"
  },
  {
    "question": "The employees at Alcott, Inc. always try to fill supply _________ as quickly as possible.",
    "choices": [
      "customers",
      "placements",
      "deliveries",
      "orders"
    ],
    "answer": "orders"
  },
  {
    "question": "Our Stellar Strands line of hair-care products will be _________ as of January 1.",
    "choices": [
      "hopeful",
      "discontinued",
      "aspiring",
      "permissive"
    ],
    "answer": "discontinued"
  },
  {
    "question": "At this time, Mr. McCauley has neither booked a flight to Berlin _________ arranged accommodations for his stay.",
    "choices": [
      "yet",
      "and",
      "nor",
      "but"
    ],
    "answer": "nor"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Edge Technology Web site _________ several tutorial videos demonstrating the various functions of its software.",
    "choices": [
      "watches",
      "remains",
      "features",
      "appears"
    ],
    "answer": "features"
  },
  {
    "question": "General audiences have proven to be more _________ of director Alvin Stern's movies than professional film critics.",
    "choices": [
      "appreciation",
      "appreciate",
      "appreciates",
      "appreciative"
    ],
    "answer": "appreciative"
  },
  {
    "question": "Uncertainty about Dextracom's future has increased _________ rumors that the CEO intends to resign.",
    "choices": [
      "amid",
      "beside",
      "above",
      "near"
    ],
    "answer": "amid"
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ all executives have had a chance to review it, the draft of the press release cannot be considered finalized.",
    "choices": [
      "Even",
      "Without",
      "Despite",
      "Unless"
    ],
    "answer": "Unless"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ms. Costanza handles all article _________ for City Scenes magazine and also assists with editing duties.",
    "choices": [
      "submit",
      "submitter",
      "submissions",
      "submitted"
    ],
    "answer": "submissions"
  },
  {
    "question": "Although sales did not meet expectations, all representatives were awarded a bonus _________ .",
    "choices": [
      "however",
      "anyway",
      "especially",
      "instead"
    ],
    "answer": "anyway"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ms. Liu sent the client an e-mail in which she _________ the urgency of a prompt reply to her questions regarding the project.",
    "choices": [
      "to explain",
      "explained",
      "explain",
      "was explained"
    ],
    "answer": "explained"
  },
  {
    "question": "The budget committee eventually agreed on a _________ for achieving its financial goals.",
    "choices": [
      "negotiation",
      "confidence",
      "result",
      "strategy"
    ],
    "answer": "strategy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Heavy snow is predicted for tomorrow morning, _________ commuters are advised to allow extra time for traffic delays.",
    "choices": [
      "during",
      "because",
      "as long as",
      "so"
    ],
    "answer": "so"
  },
  {
    "question": "This textile processing equipment was designed _________ according to the recommendations of Dr. Alejandro.",
    "choices": [
      "partly",
      "partial",
      "parts",
      "part"
    ],
    "answer": "partly"
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ eats a meal in the break room should wash and put away any dishes before returning to the office.",
    "choices": [
      "Whom",
      "Who",
      "Whoever",
      "Whose"
    ],
    "answer": "Whoever"
  },
  {
    "question": "A successful product launch will require a large amount of _________ among the company's various departments.",
    "choices": [
      "collaboration",
      "attraction",
      "initiation",
      "combination"
    ],
    "answer": "collaboration"
  },
  {
    "question": "Interviews have been set up with _________ of the four candidates under consideration for the teaching position.",
    "choices": [
      "which",
      "each",
      "these",
      "much"
    ],
    "answer": "each"
  },
  {
    "question": "As with most manufacturers, LMS Inc. is _________ to sudden changes in the price of raw materials.",
    "choices": [
      "vulnerable",
      "hesitant",
      "charged",
      "expensive"
    ],
    "answer": "vulnerable"
  },
  {
    "question": "This product review gives a thorough _________ of not only the new smartphone but also its optional accessories.",
    "choices": [
      "describe",
      "description",
      "to describe",
      "descriptive"
    ],
    "answer": "description"
  },
  {
    "question": "The design of the promotional brochure _________ to have been changed without the client's authorization.",
    "choices": [
      "formatted",
      "allowed",
      "differed",
      "seemed"
    ],
    "answer": "seemed"
  },
  {
    "question": "Unless any unexpected problems arise, construction of the new Compton Building downtown _________ precisely on schedule.",
    "choices": [
      "concluded",
      "concluding",
      "will conclude",
      "has concluded"
    ],
    "answer": "will conclude"
  },
  {
    "question": "The seminar instructor provided so much _________ information that attendees felt they had not learned much from her session.",
    "choices": [
      "accountable",
      "impatient",
      "repetitive",
      "dissatisfied"
    ],
    "answer": "repetitive"
  },
  {
    "question": "The event planner was _________ with the price quote from Joshua's Catering.",
    "choices": [
      "pleasure",
      "pleased",
      "pleasing",
      "pleasantly"
    ],
    "answer": "pleased"
  },
  {
    "question": "Because our deadline for publication is very _________, we will have to work quickly.",
    "choices": [
      "few",
      "tight",
      "small",
      "low"
    ],
    "answer": "tight"
  },
  {
    "question": "Glapper Company's financial situation has improved _________ the past few months.",
    "choices": [
      "by",
      "on",
      "of",
      "in"
    ],
    "answer": "in"
  },
  {
    "question": "A fault in the electrical system was _________ to blame for the recent drop in production at the Zurich plant.",
    "choices": [
      "excluding",
      "exclusive",
      "exclusively",
      "exclusion"
    ],
    "answer": "exclusively"
  },
  {
    "question": "Before leaving the dental clinic, please set an appointment for your next _________ checkup.",
    "choices": [
      "clean",
      "examined",
      "reminding",
      "routine"
    ],
    "answer": "routine"
  },
  {
    "question": "In addition to beach access, Grand Kohai Resort _________ features three beautiful swimming pools.",
    "choices": [
      "many",
      "other",
      "more",
      "also"
    ],
    "answer": "also"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mr. Cade and Mr. Oswald were _________ introduced at a reception late last year.",
    "choices": [
      "formality",
      "formal",
      "formals",
      "formally"
    ],
    "answer": "formally"
  },
  {
    "question": "Project leader Mia Na will monitor the activity of every member of _________ team.",
    "choices": [
      "she",
      "hers",
      "her",
      "herself"
    ],
    "answer": "her"
  },
  {
    "question": "Austin Art Supply has earned many loyal customers _________ its wide selection and friendly staff.",
    "choices": [
      "given that",
      "resulting",
      "thanks to",
      "both"
    ],
    "answer": "thanks to"
  },
  {
    "question": "The morning _________ of the customer service training workshop will take place on the seventh floor.",
    "choices": [
      "session",
      "venue",
      "instructor",
      "admission"
    ],
    "answer": "session"
  },
  {
    "question": "Brubaker Clothing's new factory will provide hundreds of jobs and other _________ benefits to the local community.",
    "choices": [
      "economist",
      "economic",
      "economically",
      "economies"
    ],
    "answer": "economic"
  },
  {
    "question": "Journalist Natalie Chen not only writes articles for the Daily Gazette _________ is a novelist as well.",
    "choices": [
      "and",
      "except",
      "but",
      "as"
    ],
    "answer": "but"
  },
  {
    "question": "Though they dislike the new policies regarding work attire, the employees _________ them.",
    "choices": [
      "following",
      "to follow",
      "will follow",
      "follows"
    ],
    "answer": "will follow"
  },
  {
    "question": "Those seeking a budget increase must provide evidence that _________ supports the need for more funding.",
    "choices": [
      "deeply",
      "hardly",
      "cordially",
      "durably"
    ],
    "answer": "deeply"
  },
  {
    "question": "Merchandise ordered through our online store is usually delivered _________ two weeks.",
    "choices": [
      "between",
      "within",
      "about",
      "less"
    ],
    "answer": "within"
  },
  {
    "question": "The artist _________ praise for the attention to detail he put into the painting of the city skyline.",
    "choices": [
      "awards",
      "deserves",
      "retrieves",
      "designs"
    ],
    "answer": "deserves"
  },
  {
    "question": "We have asked a professional contractor to calculate the _________ cost of remodeling our showroom.",
    "choices": [
      "approximate",
      "approximation",
      "approximating",
      "approximately"
    ],
    "answer": "approximate"
  },
  {
    "question": "The committee head insists that Ms. Kim must attend the next meeting, _________ it is.",
    "choices": [
      "whoever",
      "anyone",
      "everywhere",
      "whenever"
    ],
    "answer": "whenever"
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ this week, Carson City will begin a massive project to resurface public roads in November.",
    "choices": [
      "Announce",
      "Announced",
      "Announcing",
      "Announcement"
    ],
    "answer": "Announced"
  },
  {
    "question": "The delicate machinery must be carefully inspected _________ the cause of the problem to be determined.",
    "choices": [
      "such as",
      "in order for",
      "at once",
      "so that"
    ],
    "answer": "in order for"
  },
  {
    "question": "Profiles of managers and executives at _________ branch are accessible on our Web site.",
    "choices": [
      "any",
      "most",
      "entire",
      "all"
    ],
    "answer": "any"
  },
  {
    "question": "Dale Gardener, who was hired just two years ago, has quickly become one of Titan Advertising's most _________ employees.",
    "choices": [
      "valuing",
      "value",
      "valued",
      "valuation"
    ],
    "answer": "valued"
  },
  {
    "question": "A qualified jewelry appraiser can easily _________ between natural and synthetic gemstones.",
    "choices": [
      "differentiate",
      "convince",
      "assess",
      "verify"
    ],
    "answer": "differentiate"
  },
  {
    "question": "Arguments presented by supporters of the restructuring plan were stronger than those of the _________ .",
    "choices": [
      "opposes",
      "opposing",
      "opposite",
      "opposition"
    ],
    "answer": "opposition"
  },
  {
    "question": "The crew is confident that _________ progress being delayed, the construction work will finish on schedule.",
    "choices": [
      "even though",
      "in spite of",
      "on the contrary",
      "no matter"
    ],
    "answer": "in spite of"
  },
  {
    "question": "While Mr. Bradford indeed violated company safety procedure, he did not do so _________ .",
    "choices": [
      "supposedly",
      "feasibly",
      "alternatively",
      "purposely"
    ],
    "answer": "purposely"
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ the staff to make useful suggestions is a key trait of successful business managers.",
    "choices": [
      "Inspiring",
      "Inspire",
      "Inspired",
      "Inspires"
    ],
    "answer": "Inspiring"
  },
  {
    "question": "The _________ for your upcoming sales trip will be sent to you via e-mail once all of the reservations have been confirmed.",
    "choices": [
      "reserve",
      "legibility",
      "itinerary",
      "statute"
    ],
    "answer": "itinerary"
  },
  {
    "question": "The largest piece in the popular Packstar brand luggage set is _________ lightweight and easy to maneuver through airports.",
    "choices": [
      "related",
      "to relate",
      "relative",
      "relatively"
    ],
    "answer": "relatively"
  },
  {
    "question": "Conservationists made a _________ effort to persuade lawmakers to strengthen local environmental protections.",
    "choices": [
      "concerted",
      "multiple",
      "gathered",
      "respective"
    ],
    "answer": "concerted"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sales representative Reiko Nakano is _________ efficient at locating potential clients.",
    "choices": [
      "far",
      "long",
      "twice",
      "very"
    ],
    "answer": "very"
  },
  {
    "question": "We will have to take someone else's car to the airport, because _________ only seats five people.",
    "choices": [
      "myself",
      "mine",
      "my",
      "I"
    ],
    "answer": "mine"
  },
  {
    "question": "The date of the next annual clean energy symposium has already been _________ .",
    "choices": [
      "finished",
      "placed",
      "launched",
      "confirmed"
    ],
    "answer": "confirmed"
  },
  {
    "question": "Each consultant at Victor Solutions has a high level of business _________ applicable in any corporate environment.",
    "choices": [
      "expert",
      "expertly",
      "experts",
      "expertise"
    ],
    "answer": "expertise"
  },
  {
    "question": "Cooper Automotive _________ that all job applicants submit their résumés by e-mail.",
    "choices": [
      "asks",
      "to ask",
      "asking",
      "to be asked"
    ],
    "answer": "asks"
  },
  {
    "question": "The parties who sign this contract will be strictly held _________ its terms and conditions.",
    "choices": [
      "down",
      "to",
      "between",
      "with"
    ],
    "answer": "to"
  },
  {
    "question": "Pearl Street Bistro _________ its customer base by creating a rewards program that provides discounts to frequent patrons.",
    "choices": [
      "offered",
      "broadened",
      "duplicated",
      "opened"
    ],
    "answer": "broadened"
  },
  {
    "question": "Development of Restalyn's innovative skin treatment system is _________ credited to the research of Dr. Jabar.",
    "choices": [
      "widely",
      "wide",
      "widest",
      "wider"
    ],
    "answer": "widely"
  },
  {
    "question": "The warranty on the file cabinet expires on June 10, _________ which it will be too late to have the lock repaired at no cost.",
    "choices": [
      "then",
      "after",
      "for",
      "when"
    ],
    "answer": "after"
  },
  {
    "question": "Our legal department will have to review the new hiring procedures before they can be put into _________ .",
    "choices": [
      "effect",
      "effective",
      "effects",
      "effectively"
    ],
    "answer": "effect"
  },
  {
    "question": " _________ unit manufactured by Parker Electronics is carefully examined for flaws prior to packaging.",
    "choices": [
      "Anytime",
      "Total",
      "Full",
      "Every"
    ],
    "answer": "Every"
  },
  {
    "question": "Taking part in the study is _________, and participants may drop out at any time.",
    "choices": [
      "tentative",
      "reluctant",
      "voluntary",
      "willing"
    ],
    "answer": "voluntary"
  },
  {
    "question": "Diana Green's test scores were high _________, for her to be eligible to receive the Newbury Scholarship.",
    "choices": [
      "above",
      "even",
      "enough",
      "so"
    ],
    "answer": "enough"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mr. Alavario, while generally content working by _________, is always happy to be included in team projects.",
    "choices": [
      "he",
      "his",
      "him",
      "himself"
    ],
    "answer": "himself"
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ on exhibit in Melbourne, the collection of rare fossils has been moved to a museum in Sydney.",
    "choices": [
      "Previously",
      "Distantly",
      "Authentically",
      "Promptly"
    ],
    "answer": "Previously"
  },
  {
    "question": "The redecorating project was _________ conclusion when we realized the available funds had been depleted.",
    "choices": [
      "almost",
      "early for",
      "close to",
      "within"
    ],
    "answer": "close to"
  },
  {
    "question": "The National Times newspaper is renowned for its _________ edited articles and extremely informative content.",
    "choices": [
      "profession",
      "professionalism",
      "professions",
      "professionally"
    ],
    "answer": "professionally"
  },
  {
    "question": "Contrary to _________ that gasoline prices would rise throughout this year, they have instead remained remarkably steady.",
    "choices": [
      "expected",
      "expectable",
      "expect",
      "expectations"
    ],
    "answer": "expectations"
  },
  {
    "question": "The consensus _________ company executives is that our marketing strategy is ineffective and should be reconsidered.",
    "choices": [
      "throughout",
      "sharing",
      "among",
      "now"
    ],
    "answer": "among"
  },
  {
    "question": "A well-publicized report on the _________ effects of a fast-food diet inspired many people to change their eating habits.",
    "choices": [
      "harmful",
      "harm",
      "harms",
      "harmfully"
    ],
    "answer": "harmful"
  },
  {
    "question": "The policy initiative is backed by most of the staff, _________ the director has yet to grant it her authorization.",
    "choices": [
      "but",
      "nor",
      "why",
      "until"
    ],
    "answer": "but"
  },
  {
    "question": "Gia's Department Store is _________ relocation to a more densely populated part of the city.",
    "choices": [
      "transferring",
      "determining",
      "considering",
      "searching"
    ],
    "answer": "considering"
  },
  {
    "question": "Markel Flooring _________ posted a managerial opening online after Ms. Chen announced her plan to retire.",
    "choices": [
      "swift",
      "swiftest",
      "swiftly",
      "swiftness"
    ],
    "answer": "swiftly"
  },
  {
    "question": "Recent improvements at the plant have increased productivity _________ also lowering the frequency of accidents.",
    "choices": [
      "in case",
      "while",
      "and",
      "whether"
    ],
    "answer": "while"
  },
  {
    "question": "The attorney's Web site includes numerous _________ from clients expressing positive opinions of her performance.",
    "choices": [
      "aspects",
      "testimonials",
      "services",
      "backgrounds"
    ],
    "answer": "testimonials"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Shotech XG9 projector is designed to be _________ with all leading computer brands on the market.",
    "choices": [
      "usual",
      "compatible",
      "qualified",
      "mutual"
    ],
    "answer": "compatible"
  },
  {
    "question": " _________ of all the applications we have received for the internship program will probably take more than a week.",
    "choices": [
      "Screened",
      "Screen",
      "Screening",
      "To screen"
    ],
    "answer": "Screening"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mr. Delgado _________ the proposal until a cost analysis convinced him that it was not feasible.",
    "choices": [
      "is supporting",
      "will be supporting",
      "has been supporting",
      "had been supporting"
    ],
    "answer": "had been supporting"
  },
  {
    "question": "Documentation of business expenses is required _________ claim a tax exemption.",
    "choices": [
      "in order to",
      "concerning",
      "on account of",
      "as for"
    ],
    "answer": "in order to"
  },
  {
    "question": "Both _________ and visual appeal contributed to the success of Duval's new line of footwear.",
    "choices": [
      "durability",
      "reliance",
      "cause",
      "option"
    ],
    "answer": "durability"
  },
  {
    "question": "The nature documentary Life in Blue earned critical acclaim _________ its masterful cinematography.",
    "choices": [
      "throughout",
      "for",
      "because",
      "apart"
    ],
    "answer": "for"
  },
  {
    "question": "A _________ way for a new firm to establish name recognition in the area is to sponsor local sporting events.",
    "choices": [
      "sense",
      "sensing",
      "sensible",
      "sensibly"
    ],
    "answer": "sensible"
  },
  {
    "question": "Phillip Carmichael is _________ to serve Pacific City in his new capacity as Mayor.",
    "choices": [
      "proud",
      "genuine",
      "complete",
      "purposeful"
    ],
    "answer": "proud"
  },
  {
    "question": "Modern appliances have been installed in each _________ unit of the apartment building.",
    "choices": [
      "resident",
      "residential",
      "residency",
      "reside"
    ],
    "answer": "residential"
  },
  {
    "question": "The _________ of restrictions on work attire was met with approval by most of our employees.",
    "choices": [
      "loosening",
      "loosens",
      "loosen",
      "loosest"
    ],
    "answer": "loosening"
  },
  {
    "question": "Recent attempts to _________ tourism have greatly benefited the local economy on Teague Island.",
    "choices": [
      "express",
      "boost",
      "reach",
      "surpass"
    ],
    "answer": "boost"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the event of malfunction, bring the camera to a qualified repair shop rather than attempting to fix it on _________ .",
    "choices": [
      "yourself",
      "your own",
      "you",
      "yours"
    ],
    "answer": "your own"
  },
  {
    "question": "Only a small number of _________ to our invitations remain to be received.",
    "choices": [
      "replies",
      "replying",
      "replied",
      "reply"
    ],
    "answer": "replies"
  },
  {
    "question": "The extension of the recruiting drive by a week resulted from a _________ of eligible candidates.",
    "choices": [
      "frequency",
      "vacancy",
      "few",
      "scarcity"
    ],
    "answer": "scarcity"
  },
  {
    "question": "Successful completion of the program _________ participation in several outdoor training exercises.",
    "choices": [
      "involve",
      "is involved",
      "involving",
      "involves"
    ],
    "answer": "involves"
  },
  {
    "question": "Darrow Contracting Service uses only top-quality construction materials bought _________ reputable suppliers.",
    "choices": [
      "from",
      "into",
      "out",
      "upon"
    ],
    "answer": "from"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ms. Aoki and Ms. Iger seem to be _________ compatible and enjoy working together every day.",
    "choices": [
      "much",
      "highly",
      "abruptly",
      "near"
    ],
    "answer": "highly"
  },
  {
    "question": "Please follow the current hiring guidelines _________ they are changed in September.",
    "choices": [
      "without",
      "rather",
      "otherwise",
      "until"
    ],
    "answer": "until"
  },
  {
    "question": "The _________ of tomorrow's meeting is to resolve the issues that are slowing our progress on the Simpson account.",
    "choices": [
      "matter",
      "dedication",
      "point",
      "success"
    ],
    "answer": "point"
  },
  {
    "question": "Brookfield Inn boasts _________ rooms than those of the Royal Crest Hotel.",
    "choices": [
      "large",
      "larger",
      "largely",
      "largest"
    ],
    "answer": "larger"
  },
  {
    "question": "This tumble dryer contains an automatic shutoff mechanism _________ main purpose is to prevent the machine from overheating.",
    "choices": [
      "that",
      "whose",
      "which",
      "what"
    ],
    "answer": "whose"
  },
  {
    "question": "Customer service at independently owned businesses is _________ better than at corporate chains.",
    "choices": [
      "more common",
      "common",
      "commonality",
      "commonly"
    ],
    "answer": "commonly"
  },
  {
    "question": "Lydia Dupree's upcoming exhibit will showcase sculptures _________ by her recent travels abroad.",
    "choices": [
      "experienced",
      "reminded",
      "persuaded",
      "inspired"
    ],
    "answer": "inspired"
  },
  {
    "question": "Make sure to remain perfectly still _________ the photographer takes the picture for your ID badge.",
    "choices": [
      "whereas",
      "ever",
      "while",
      "during"
    ],
    "answer": "while"
  },
  {
    "question": "Dr. Colbert's nomination for the Huntz Prize is one of the most _________ achievements of his scientific career.",
    "choices": [
      "gifted",
      "talkative",
      "notable",
      "grateful"
    ],
    "answer": "notable"
  },
  {
    "question": "When some _________ safety violations were reported to plant officials, an investigation was promptly scheduled.",
    "choices": [
      "apparent",
      "apparently",
      "appearance",
      "appearances"
    ],
    "answer": "apparent"
  },
  {
    "question": "Due to the play's popularity, we recommend that seat _________ be made well in advance.",
    "choices": [
      "admissions",
      "expectations",
      "positions",
      "reservations"
    ],
    "answer": "reservations"
  },
  {
    "question": "After the presentation next Tuesday, the board _________ whether or not the budget proposal is feasible.",
    "choices": [
      "to discuss",
      "discussing",
      "will discuss",
      "has discussed"
    ],
    "answer": "will discuss"
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ the request for more funding was declined, the scientists will have to suspend their research.",
    "choices": [
      "Unless",
      "Since",
      "Although",
      "Once"
    ],
    "answer": "Since"
  },
  {
    "question": "As the repaving work is slated _________ soon, work crews are preparing to block the affected roads off to through traffic.",
    "choices": [
      "to begin",
      "begun",
      "will have begun",
      "beginning"
    ],
    "answer": "to begin"
  },
  {
    "question": "With _________ of the consumer survey complete, development of our promotional strategy can now begin.",
    "choices": [
      "analytic",
      "analysis",
      "analyze",
      "analyzed"
    ],
    "answer": "analysis"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mr. Erickson, who was once _________ opposed to the recycling initiative, is now one of its biggest supporters.",
    "choices": [
      "adamantly",
      "preferably",
      "dependently",
      "avoidably"
    ],
    "answer": "adamantly"
  },
  {
    "question": "It takes just _________ of one hour by taxi to reach the Banner Convention Center from Rochester Airport.",
    "choices": [
      "below",
      "less",
      "short",
      "within"
    ],
    "answer": "short"
  },
  {
    "question": "Workers are not _________ asked to transfer departments during their first six months of employment.",
    "choices": [
      "customization",
      "customize",
      "customarily",
      "customary"
    ],
    "answer": "customarily"
  },
  {
    "question": "Scarlet Chou is among the group of honorees being _________ at tonight's annual awards banquet.",
    "choices": [
      "appraised",
      "implemented",
      "devoted",
      "recognized"
    ],
    "answer": "recognized"
  },
  {
    "question": "When Ms. Kim arrives, please give _________ an update on the status of our project.",
    "choices": [
      "herself",
      "hers",
      "her",
      "she"
    ],
    "answer": "her"
  },
  {
    "question": "Consumer testing of RayBlok's new sunscreen will be _________ at major outdoor events this summer.",
    "choices": [
      "conducted",
      "transacted",
      "driven",
      "contracted"
    ],
    "answer": "conducted"
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ from Mr. Sparrow, the directors were unanimous in their approval of the purchase of the new office space.",
    "choices": [
      "Apart",
      "Besides",
      "Against",
      "Other"
    ],
    "answer": "Apart"
  },
  {
    "question": "The board _________ positively to the ideas of the new marketing director.",
    "choices": [
      "reacting",
      "reactive",
      "reactively",
      "reacted"
    ],
    "answer": "reacted"
  },
  {
    "question": "The _________ voucher is redeemable for a 15 percent discount on your next purchase at Penny Smart.",
    "choices": [
      "satisfied",
      "enclosed",
      "compensated",
      "regarded"
    ],
    "answer": "enclosed"
  },
  {
    "question": "Efficiency at the plant will _________ increase as new assembly procedures are adopted.",
    "choices": [
      "steady",
      "steadying",
      "steadily",
      "steadiness"
    ],
    "answer": "steadily"
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ guidebooks rank Platinum Suites as the area's top hotel, the Starlight Inn has received better online reviews.",
    "choices": [
      "Regardless",
      "While",
      "Despite",
      "Always"
    ],
    "answer": "While"
  },
  {
    "question": "Parties without reservations are not guaranteed _________ at our restaurant.",
    "choices": [
      "service",
      "are serving",
      "served",
      "to serve"
    ],
    "answer": "service"
  },
  {
    "question": "The results of the clinical trial of the new medication are truly remarkable in light of the _________ outcome.",
    "choices": [
      "predict",
      "predicting",
      "predicted",
      "prediction"
    ],
    "answer": "predicted"
  },
  {
    "question": "The contents were _________ from the box so that it could be used for other purposes.",
    "choices": [
      "avoided",
      "refrained",
      "emptied",
      "departed"
    ],
    "answer": "emptied"
  },
  {
    "question": " _________ the end of this week, the contractor will have completed the remodeling work.",
    "choices": [
      "Once",
      "By",
      "Sure",
      "To"
    ],
    "answer": "By"
  },
  {
    "question": "Stage productions with _________ of more than a hundred are held at Cliffside Auditorium.",
    "choices": [
      "sizes",
      "seats",
      "venues",
      "casts"
    ],
    "answer": "casts"
  },
  {
    "question": "Customers can count _________ Williams & Sons to maintain the best selection of home appliances in Newport City.",
    "choices": [
      "up",
      "for",
      "on",
      "at"
    ],
    "answer": "on"
  },
  {
    "question": "Emergency _________ undergo an extensive training program before they can receive certification.",
    "choices": [
      "medics",
      "medically",
      "medical",
      "medicine"
    ],
    "answer": "medics"
  },
  {
    "question": " _________ test takers to achieve a passing score, they must answer at least eighty percent of the questions correctly.",
    "choices": [
      "In case of",
      "To be certain",
      "In order for",
      "For instance"
    ],
    "answer": "In order for"
  },
  {
    "question": "People who take frequent trips abroad tend _________ bookings farther in advance than less experienced travelers.",
    "choices": [
      "have made",
      "made",
      "to make",
      "making"
    ],
    "answer": "to make"
  },
  {
    "question": "The musical attracts _________ large audiences that tickets are always in short supply.",
    "choices": [
      "very",
      "such",
      "so",
      "more"
    ],
    "answer": "such"
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ of the iconic Tarpin Bridge is set to begin during the first week of August.",
    "choices": [
      "Distraction",
      "Restoration",
      "Generation",
      "Variation"
    ],
    "answer": "Restoration"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Blueberry Inn holds guests _________ for any damage they cause to the rooms.",
    "choices": [
      "accounts",
      "accounted",
      "accountancy",
      "accountable"
    ],
    "answer": "accountable"
  },
  {
    "question": "Management implemented stricter safety guidelines for machine operators, _________ reducing the likelihood of an accident.",
    "choices": [
      "so that",
      "thus",
      "which",
      "such as"
    ],
    "answer": "thus"
  },
  {
    "question": "Su-Li Ming _________ a position at Nardcot Industries by impressing the recruiters during her interviews.",
    "choices": [
      "presumed",
      "offered",
      "adopted",
      "secured"
    ],
    "answer": "secured"
  },
  {
    "question": "Miriam Cosmetics' new mascara line is its most popular _________, and retailers are struggling to keep it in stock.",
    "choices": [
      "far",
      "before",
      "yet",
      "way"
    ],
    "answer": "yet"
  },
  {
    "question": "Owing _________ to its central location, The Pines apartment complex seldom has vacancies.",
    "choices": [
      "greatly",
      "greater",
      "great",
      "greats"
    ],
    "answer": "greatly"
  },
  {
    "question": "To show our _________ to improving the local community, we urge employees to volunteer with area charities.",
    "choices": [
      "judgment",
      "development",
      "management",
      "commitment"
    ],
    "answer": "commitment"
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ Mr. James had publicly announced his plans to move to London, he decided to remain working in Seoul.",
    "choices": [
      "Except for",
      "Although",
      "In spite of",
      "Wherever"
    ],
    "answer": "Although"
  },
  {
    "question": "There has been no difficulty so far, but the shift changes could lead to _________ scheduling problems.",
    "choices": [
      "consensual",
      "manual",
      "eventual",
      "punctual"
    ],
    "answer": "eventual"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mr. Li and Ms. Day disagreed on a few details of the promotion, but _________ believed the overall strategy was sound.",
    "choices": [
      "both",
      "one another",
      "each other",
      "other"
    ],
    "answer": "both"
  },
  {
    "question": "Designers can use this software to create original graphics and artwork _________ to manipulate and alter digital photography.",
    "choices": [
      "as well as",
      "rather",
      "along with",
      "in addition"
    ],
    "answer": "as well as"
  },
  {
    "question": "Your membership in the Bayonne Professionals' Group _________ once your credentials are brought back up to date.",
    "choices": [
      "had reinstated",
      "will be reinstated",
      "was reinstating",
      "has been reinstating"
    ],
    "answer": "will be reinstated"
  },
  {
    "question": "This book will equip business owners with the tools and knowledge they need to _________ a profit within a short time.",
    "choices": [
      "inquire",
      "captivate",
      "deploy",
      "realize"
    ],
    "answer": "realize"
  },
  {
    "question": "All FFP employees are encouraged to participate _________ in community programs.\n",
    "choices": [
      "regularly",
      "regular",
      "regulation",
      "regularity"
    ],
    "answer": "regularly"
  },
  {
    "question": "Please inspect the contents of the package and contact us with any _________.\n",
    "choices": [
      "questionable",
      "questioning",
      "questioned",
      "questions"
    ],
    "answer": "questions"
  },
  {
    "question": "The training instructors will stay at the _________ renovated guest house.\n",
    "choices": [
      "newly",
      "enough",
      "directly",
      "exactly"
    ],
    "answer": "newly"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sunnyville Public Library is _________ today because of a problem with the electrical system.\n",
    "choices": [
      "certain",
      "closed",
      "returned",
      "simple"
    ],
    "answer": "closed"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ms. Suzuki _________ as a leader in the Asian financial services industry.\n",
    "choices": [
      "recognizes",
      "recognizing",
      "is recognized",
      "has recognized"
    ],
    "answer": "is recognized"
  },
  {
    "question": "Before meeting with the board, Mr. Ortiz practiced his _________ several times.\n",
    "choices": [
      "presentation",
      "leader",
      "setting",
      "education"
    ],
    "answer": "presentation"
  },
  {
    "question": "The firm's _________ strategy is quite different from that of its competitors.\n",
    "choices": [
      "hired",
      "to hire",
      "hires",
      "hiring"
    ],
    "answer": "hiring"
  },
  {
    "question": "Before the cafeteria's expansion, a limited number of employees could _________ the seating area at one time.\n",
    "choices": [
      "access",
      "accessibly",
      "accessing",
      "to access"
    ],
    "answer": "access"
  },
  {
    "question": "The proposal from _________ development team was met with great enthusiasm.\n",
    "choices": [
      "us",
      "we",
      "ours",
      "our"
    ],
    "answer": "our"
  },
  {
    "question": "At Triton Bank, new employees have 30 days to _________ in the company's benefits program.\n",
    "choices": [
      "credit",
      "renew",
      "commit",
      "enroll"
    ],
    "answer": "enroll"
  },
  {
    "question": "Epiquick Production Services hired a _________ speaker to boost employee morale.\n",
    "choices": [
      "motivational",
      "motivate",
      "to motivate",
      "motivates"
    ],
    "answer": "motivational"
  },
  {
    "question": "The branch office in Riyadh will be closed on Thursday and Friday _________ a national holiday.\n",
    "choices": [
      "at",
      "of",
      "for",
      "with"
    ],
    "answer": "for"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ms. Patel _________ offered to share the results of her research with the planning board.\n",
    "choices": [
      "generosity",
      "most generous",
      "generously",
      "generous"
    ],
    "answer": "generously"
  },
  {
    "question": "The training session will begin fifteen minutes late _________ Ms. Stumpff is still in a meeting.\n",
    "choices": [
      "as",
      "then",
      "or",
      "but"
    ],
    "answer": "as"
  },
  {
    "question": "Skyspan Airlines compensated passengers whose flights _________ due to crew shortage.\n",
    "choices": [
      "cancel",
      "to be canceled",
      "were canceled",
      "canceling"
    ],
    "answer": "were canceled"
  },
  {
    "question": "Over the past six months, there has been a tremendous _________ for Hudson's motorized bicycles.\n",
    "choices": [
      "amount",
      "demand",
      "speed",
      "service"
    ],
    "answer": "demand"
  },
  {
    "question": "The marketing director is _________ in the latest Web site design than in the previous ones.\n",
    "choices": [
      "more interested",
      "most interested",
      "too interested",
      "interested"
    ],
    "answer": "more interested"
  },
  {
    "question": "November's sales figures were _________ high given the poor weather conditions during that month.\n",
    "choices": [
      "primarily",
      "surprisingly",
      "separately",
      "accurately"
    ],
    "answer": "surprisingly"
  },
  {
    "question": "Camico Broadband Services earned excellent ratings for _________ on the latest consumer survey.\n",
    "choices": [
      "reliable",
      "reliability",
      "reliably",
      "rely"
    ],
    "answer": "reliability"
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ volunteered to complete the report, so Ms. Hughes assigned it to Mr. Nakamura.\n",
    "choices": [
      "Have not",
      "Having nobody",
      "No one",
      "No"
    ],
    "answer": "No one"
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ the guidance of a talented coach, Belfast's chess team has made great progress.\n",
    "choices": [
      "Under",
      "Along",
      "Toward",
      "Among"
    ],
    "answer": "Under"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mr. Lukas e-mailed his staff to ask whether _________ would be available to cover the front desk from noon to 1 P.M.\n",
    "choices": [
      "other",
      "himself",
      "few",
      "anyone"
    ],
    "answer": "anyone"
  },
  {
    "question": "Bluing, Inc., combined its two warehouses in order to _________ the efficiency of its operations.\n",
    "choices": [
      "collapse",
      "maximize",
      "astonish",
      "resemble"
    ],
    "answer": "maximize"
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ he is scheduled for a promotion, Anton Shaqua plans to leave the law firm soon.\n",
    "choices": [
      "Although",
      "Prior to",
      "From",
      "Perhaps"
    ],
    "answer": "Although"
  },
  {
    "question": "Margolex' survey results were _________ analyzed using state-of-the-art software.\n",
    "choices": [
      "brightly",
      "thickly",
      "boastfully",
      "effortlessly"
    ],
    "answer": "effortlessly"
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ Zamlo toys are sold primarily in Australia, they are manufactured in Malaysia.\n",
    "choices": [
      "Despite",
      "Even",
      "While",
      "That"
    ],
    "answer": "While"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ms. Cho asked her secretary to compile a list of caterers _________ menus include vegetarian options.\n",
    "choices": [
      "who",
      "whom",
      "whose",
      "whoever"
    ],
    "answer": "whose"
  },
  {
    "question": "The customer who called to complain had received an _________ tracking number.\n",
    "choices": [
      "unheard",
      "absent",
      "inaccurate",
      "opposite"
    ],
    "answer": "inaccurate"
  },
  {
    "question": "After 25 years of use, Burl Business Solutions has decided to _________ its well-known logo.\n",
    "choices": [
      "approach",
      "retire",
      "reduce",
      "appoint"
    ],
    "answer": "retire"
  },
  {
    "question": "Any _________ to the company's work-from-home policy must be approved by the Human Resources Department.\n",
    "choices": [
      "inspection",
      "exception",
      "to attend",
      "correlation"
    ],
    "answer": "exception"
  },
  {
    "question": "Summer interns at Fairview City Hall must _________ all city council meetings.\n",
    "choices": [
      "attend",
      "attending",
      "to attend",
      "attends"
    ],
    "answer": "attend"
  },
  {
    "question": "A _________ analysis of market trends can lead retailers to profitable results.\n",
    "choices": [
      "careful",
      "care",
      "carefully",
      "cared"
    ],
    "answer": "careful"
  },
  {
    "question": "Please _________ a copy of each sales report on a separate piece of paper.\n",
    "choices": [
      "pick",
      "tell",
      "reply",
      "print"
    ],
    "answer": "print"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ms. Wendt's _________, Daniel Novianto, will be answering her e-mails while she is on leave.\n",
    "choices": [
      "assistant",
      "assistance",
      "assisting",
      "assists"
    ],
    "answer": "assistant"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not keep perishable foods in the cooler beyond _________ expiration date.\n",
    "choices": [
      "they",
      "their",
      "them",
      "themselves"
    ],
    "answer": "their"
  },
  {
    "question": "Erico Costa's new work of fiction is an _________ tale of mistaken identity.\n",
    "choices": [
      "amuse",
      "amusement",
      "amusingly",
      "amusing"
    ],
    "answer": "amusing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Zantos Network is moving forward with the _________ to purchase a local radio station.\n",
    "choices": [
      "property",
      "advancement",
      "proposal",
      "signature"
    ],
    "answer": "proposal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Over 95 percent of Kapp Hardware's clients have responded _________ in online reviews.\n",
    "choices": [
      "favorable",
      "favorably",
      "favored",
      "to favor"
    ],
    "answer": "favorably"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ms. Kean mentioned the improved tool kit _________ at the meeting but did not discuss how we will promote it.\n",
    "choices": [
      "closely",
      "repeatedly",
      "upwardly",
      "neatly"
    ],
    "answer": "repeatedly"
  },
  {
    "question": "Once Mr. Braun had toured the conference _________ he paid the deposit fee.\n",
    "choices": [
      "location",
      "locate",
      "locating",
      "locator"
    ],
    "answer": "location"
  },
  {
    "question": "Management has asked Ms. Leung to meet _________ the new office supply vendor tomorrow.\n",
    "choices": [
      "at",
      "with",
      "for",
      "of"
    ],
    "answer": "with"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mr. Farmingham will rearrange his schedule to have lunch at 2:00 P.M. _________ you are available then.\n",
    "choices": [
      "if",
      "by",
      "without",
      "during"
    ],
    "answer": "if"
  },
  {
    "question": "Please include your employee number _________ filling out the room reservation form.\n",
    "choices": [
      "although",
      "so",
      "when",
      "however"
    ],
    "answer": "when"
  },
  {
    "question": "Be sure to pack a water bottle for tomorrow's mountain hike, as it is _________ to stay hydrated.\n",
    "choices": [
      "nutritious",
      "sensitive",
      "direct",
      "crucial"
    ],
    "answer": "crucial"
  },
  {
    "question": "Westmont Hospital announced that leading heart _________ Dr. Emily Chow will be joining the staff next month.\n",
    "choices": [
      "special",
      "specialize",
      "specialist",
      "specialized"
    ],
    "answer": "specialist"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Midosuji branch of Tsurutani Bank is closed _________ because of a problem with the electrical system.\n",
    "choices": [
      "slightly",
      "temporarily",
      "universally",
      "terminally"
    ],
    "answer": "temporarily"
  },
  {
    "question": "Funds raised by the community auction will be used to maintain the _________ Quill Street playground.\n",
    "choices": [
      "aging",
      "glad",
      "utter",
      "brief"
    ],
    "answer": "aging"
  },
  {
    "question": "United Carpet West received _________ higher customer satisfaction ratings than its competitors did.\n",
    "choices": [
      "signify",
      "significance",
      "signifying",
      "significantly"
    ],
    "answer": "significantly"
  },
  {
    "question": "This month's tool catalog was edited to reflect that two items are not in _________.\n",
    "choices": [
      "situation",
      "stock",
      "action",
      "asset"
    ],
    "answer": "stock"
  },
  {
    "question": "On-site training programs are associated with _________ employee motivation.\n",
    "choices": [
      "to increase",
      "increases",
      "increased",
      "increase"
    ],
    "answer": "increased"
  },
  {
    "question": "The catering contract calls for flowers to be arranged _________ in a vase on each banquet table.\n",
    "choices": [
      "honestly",
      "enormously",
      "hungrily",
      "attractively"
    ],
    "answer": "attractively"
  },
  {
    "question": "Fifty percent of the total landscaping cost is required now, and the _________ is due upon completion of the project.\n",
    "choices": [
      "remains",
      "remain",
      "remained",
      "remainder"
    ],
    "answer": "remainder"
  },
  {
    "question": "The date of the building's grand opening was moved _________ President Daniels could be there to officiate.\n",
    "choices": [
      "so that",
      "such as",
      "due to",
      "except for"
    ],
    "answer": "so that"
  },
  {
    "question": "New patients _________ miss their initial visit at Pratha Medical Clinic without advance notice will not be rescheduled.\n",
    "choices": [
      "what",
      "where",
      "who",
      "why"
    ],
    "answer": "who"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mr. Lewis deserves _________ for the thoughtful service he always provides to customers.\n",
    "choices": [
      "content",
      "experience",
      "community",
      "recognition"
    ],
    "answer": "recognition"
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ the growing demand for steel, there is still a large supply available.\n",
    "choices": [
      "Likewise",
      "Despite",
      "Though",
      "While"
    ],
    "answer": "Despite"
  },
  {
    "question": "Maria Pennfield's Star Signs Company _________ two decades ago.\n",
    "choices": [
      "has established",
      "establishes",
      "was established",
      "establishing"
    ],
    "answer": "was established"
  },
  {
    "question": "The paintings _________ the outside wall of the Klampton Hotel feature the art of Ah Lam Zhang.\n",
    "choices": [
      "unto",
      "instead of",
      "in case of",
      "along"
    ],
    "answer": "along"
  },
  {
    "question": "Please _________ the handrail when going down the Palmer Theater's marble staircase.\n",
    "choices": [
      "catch up",
      "run out of",
      "find out",
      "hold on to"
    ],
    "answer": "hold on to"
  },
  {
    "question": "Until the office heating system _________, employees are permitted to work from home.\n",
    "choices": [
      "will be fixed",
      "is being fixed",
      "has been fixed",
      "had been fixed"
    ],
    "answer": "has been fixed"
  },
  {
    "question": "Duray Airlines offers delicious food and beverage _________.\n",
    "choices": [
      "fees",
      "answers",
      "options",
      "tasks"
    ],
    "answer": "options"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Oakshore region _________ large numbers of young professionals.\n",
    "choices": [
      "was attracted",
      "has been attracted",
      "attracting",
      "attracts"
    ],
    "answer": "attracts"
  },
  {
    "question": "The sales report is due tomorrow, so please finish it _________.\n",
    "choices": [
      "easily",
      "quickly",
      "certainly",
      "truly"
    ],
    "answer": "quickly"
  },
  {
    "question": "Referring to the _________ in the user's manual will help you to identify the parts of the workbench.\n",
    "choices": [
      "illustrate",
      "illustrator",
      "illustration",
      "illustrated"
    ],
    "answer": "illustration"
  },
  {
    "question": "No more than four passengers are permitted in _________ taxi operated by the Halligan Company.\n",
    "choices": [
      "any",
      "all",
      "some",
      "such"
    ],
    "answer": "any"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sales of the Moro Camera dropped by 3 percent _________ the last quarter.\n",
    "choices": [
      "down",
      "well",
      "and",
      "during"
    ],
    "answer": "during"
  },
  {
    "question": "The newest branch of the library is located _________ Pine Street, directly across from the post office.\n",
    "choices": [
      "into",
      "among",
      "until",
      "on"
    ],
    "answer": "on"
  },
  {
    "question": "The property manager must ensure that renters understand _________ rental agreement.\n",
    "choices": [
      "their",
      "they",
      "theirs",
      "them"
    ],
    "answer": "their"
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ Ms. Bai was not available to lead the board meeting, she was able to find a replacement.\n",
    "choices": [
      "Although",
      "Whether",
      "Instead",
      "Accordingly"
    ],
    "answer": "Although"
  },
  {
    "question": "Once staff has had training in the new accounting software, they will be prepared to work _________.\n",
    "choices": [
      "independent",
      "independently",
      "independency",
      "independence"
    ],
    "answer": "independently"
  },
  {
    "question": "Nuts from Quintana Orchards can be a _________ source of vitamins and minerals for a nutritious diet.\n",
    "choices": [
      "long",
      "various",
      "rich",
      "careful"
    ],
    "answer": "rich"
  },
  {
    "question": "To maintain the Cheerbrew coffeemaker properly, wipe it with a _________ sponge after each use.\n",
    "choices": [
      "moist",
      "moistens",
      "moistly",
      "moisten"
    ],
    "answer": "moist"
  },
  {
    "question": "Research shows that an online marketing strategy is vital for survival in the _________ competitive athletic shoe market.\n",
    "choices": [
      "skillfully",
      "increasingly",
      "accidentally",
      "meaningfully"
    ],
    "answer": "increasingly"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tomorrow's session will train participants on _________ to prepare containers for overseas shipments.\n",
    "choices": [
      "what",
      "how",
      "that",
      "then"
    ],
    "answer": "how"
  },
  {
    "question": "Applications received _________ the October 15 deadline will not be processed.\n",
    "choices": [
      "after",
      "already",
      "while",
      "often"
    ],
    "answer": "after"
  },
  {
    "question": "Customers expressed dissatisfaction with the cost of the phone, but complaints about the user interface were relatively _________.\n",
    "choices": [
      "rarest",
      "rare",
      "rarity",
      "rarely"
    ],
    "answer": "rare"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tickets to the museum's special exhibit may be ordered in advance on the Web site _________ purchased upon arrival.\n",
    "choices": [
      "or",
      "for",
      "where",
      "since"
    ],
    "answer": "or"
  },
  {
    "question": "Two water-quality studies, which _________ last week, reflect the hard work of the Water Resource Council to keep local water clean.\n",
    "choices": [
      "were released",
      "were being released",
      "had released",
      "had been releasing"
    ],
    "answer": "were released"
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ the efforts of cycling enthusiasts, the proposal to resurface bicycle paths in County Kildare was defeated yesterday.\n",
    "choices": [
      "Throughout",
      "Besides",
      "Despite",
      "Versus"
    ],
    "answer": "Despite"
  },
  {
    "question": "Crum Carpeting's profits have risen _________ since the company introduced a new environmentally friendly carpet line.\n",
    "choices": [
      "steadiness",
      "steadying",
      "steadily",
      "steadied"
    ],
    "answer": "steadily"
  },
  {
    "question": "Glideline Technologies _________ in archiving records and retrieving lost data.\n",
    "choices": [
      "consists",
      "interests",
      "inspects",
      "specializes"
    ],
    "answer": "specializes"
  },
  {
    "question": "The mayoral candidates are competing for television _________.\n",
    "choices": [
      "having exposed",
      "exposed",
      "expose",
      "exposure"
    ],
    "answer": "exposure"
  },
  {
    "question": "Employees should submit time sheets by noon today _________ the payroll office can distribute paychecks on schedule.\n",
    "choices": [
      "so that",
      "in order to",
      "that is",
      "in case of"
    ],
    "answer": "so that"
  },
  {
    "question": "Suburban residents are _________ in favor of expanding Highway 589 to relieve traffic congestion.\n",
    "choices": [
      "overwhelm",
      "overwhelmingly",
      "overwhelming",
      "overwhelms"
    ],
    "answer": "overwhelmingly"
  },
  {
    "question": "Business travel is _________ for Shawton Associates by Young-Pyo Kim at Wright Air Transit.\n",
    "choices": [
      "equipped",
      "attributed",
      "coordinated",
      "concurred"
    ],
    "answer": "coordinated"
  },
  {
    "question": "Most models of the Remagine laptop computer now come with a _________ keyboard.\n",
    "choices": [
      "removability",
      "remove",
      "removable",
      "remover"
    ],
    "answer": "removable"
  },
  {
    "question": "With the recent surge in electronic sales, industry analysts are anticipating that the device-to-person _________ will soon surpass earlier predictions.\n",
    "choices": [
      "division",
      "fraction",
      "part",
      "ratio"
    ],
    "answer": "ratio"
  },
  {
    "question": "In response to consumer complaints, assembly instructions for the model 481 bookshelf have been _________.\n",
    "choices": [
      "acknowledged",
      "estimated",
      "controlled",
      "simplified"
    ],
    "answer": "simplified"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose an _________ sized air conditioner for your company's needs, as larger models use more energy.\n",
    "choices": [
      "affirmatively",
      "appropriately",
      "unexpectedly",
      "extensively"
    ],
    "answer": "appropriately"
  },
  {
    "question": "Owing to his knowledge of historic buildings, Luis Harmon was _________ to lead the Main Street Restoration Project.\n",
    "choices": [
      "persuasion",
      "persuasively",
      "persuaded",
      "persuading"
    ],
    "answer": "persuaded"
  },
  {
    "question": "Most of our clients are _________ about the prospect of our showroom moving to a larger space.\n",
    "choices": [
      "exciting",
      "to excite",
      "excites",
      "excited"
    ],
    "answer": "excited"
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ their review of the documents, Ms. Oliveira will make changes to the paperwork.\n",
    "choices": [
      "After",
      "Now",
      "Soon",
      "Next"
    ],
    "answer": "After"
  },
  {
    "question": "Contact technical support for any needed _________ with software issues.\n",
    "choices": [
      "assist",
      "assistant",
      "assisted",
      "assistance"
    ],
    "answer": "assistance"
  },
  {
    "question": "Willington Hair Salon will be open _________ in weekend starting May.\n",
    "choices": [
      "every",
      "from",
      "enough",
      "since"
    ],
    "answer": "every"
  },
  {
    "question": "When accessing _________ billing statement online, be sure to look for new discount offers.\n",
    "choices": [
      "yourselves",
      "yours",
      "your",
      "you"
    ],
    "answer": "your"
  },
  {
    "question": "The work shifts at Stella's Confectionary are eight hours long and _________ a 30-minute break for lunch.\n",
    "choices": [
      "prepare",
      "release",
      "assemble",
      "include"
    ],
    "answer": "include"
  },
  {
    "question": "The timer on the lamp is designed to turn it off _________ to reduce energy use.\n",
    "choices": [
      "automatic",
      "automatically",
      "automated",
      "automate"
    ],
    "answer": "automatically"
  },
  {
    "question": "Employees who will be commuting to the Foster Street facility should request parking permits _________ the end of the month.\n",
    "choices": [
      "under",
      "against",
      "along",
      "before"
    ],
    "answer": "before"
  },
  {
    "question": "Our Italian wool jackets are _________ for many occasions, from a formal dinner to a casual evening with friends.\n",
    "choices": [
      "to suit",
      "suitably",
      "suitable",
      "suit"
    ],
    "answer": "suitable"
  },
  {
    "question": "Dale Department Store will have a special sale on jewelry _________ before the holidays.\n",
    "choices": [
      "sensitively",
      "extremely",
      "immediately",
      "figuratively"
    ],
    "answer": "immediately"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mr. Hobbes _________ a sincere interest in a long-term career at Lassen Bank.\n",
    "choices": [
      "expressed",
      "pointed",
      "arranged",
      "studied"
    ],
    "answer": "expressed"
  },
  {
    "question": "The carpet in the lobby of the Chiang Mai Opera House will be replaced with material _________ is easier to maintain.\n",
    "choices": [
      "what",
      "where",
      "that",
      "this"
    ],
    "answer": "that"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hunt's Gift Shop carries a wide selection of _________, including the Swinnville Daily News and West Bay Monthly.\n",
    "choices": [
      "publication",
      "publications",
      "publish",
      "published"
    ],
    "answer": "publications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Engineers in the Welber Machine Factory in Cologne work to correct minor flaws in the designs of _________ drilling systems.\n",
    "choices": [
      "confused",
      "complex",
      "informative",
      "cautious"
    ],
    "answer": "complex"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the plumbing problem _________, we recommend that you contact the product manufacturer.\n",
    "choices": [
      "to persist",
      "was persisting",
      "persists",
      "persistence"
    ],
    "answer": "persists"
  },
  {
    "question": "You will receive a _________ e-mail from the Nicoya Hotel verifying your travel plans within two hours of making your reservation.\n",
    "choices": [
      "sponsor",
      "confirmation",
      "margin",
      "permit"
    ],
    "answer": "confirmation"
  },
  {
    "question": "Move-It Storage provides a variety of container sizes to help store belongings _________.\n",
    "choices": [
      "compact",
      "compactly",
      "compacted",
      "compacting"
    ],
    "answer": "compactly"
  },
  {
    "question": "The new plant director, Ha-Jae Cheon, will be _________ for reducing the maintenance costs at the Tamarindo facility.\n",
    "choices": [
      "fortunate",
      "possible",
      "senseless",
      "responsible"
    ],
    "answer": "responsible"
  },
  {
    "question": "Leffert's Market will close two hours earlier _________ usual next Tuesday.\n",
    "choices": [
      "than",
      "but",
      "above",
      "when"
    ],
    "answer": "than"
  },
  {
    "question": "Caldwell Computers accepts returns _________ products have not been removed from the packaging.\n",
    "choices": [
      "in order that",
      "such as",
      "in case",
      "as long as"
    ],
    "answer": "as long as"
  }, 
  {
    "question": "Until last month Kanyan, Inc., _________ farming equipment for CEK Agriculture.\n",
    "choices": [
      "manufacturing",
      "manufactured",
      "is manufacturing",
      "was manufactured"
    ],
    "answer": "manufactured"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sign up now for deals available _________ to Platinum members of the Bordner Gym Club.\n",
    "choices": [
      "exclusively",
      "financially",
      "relatively",
      "productively"
    ],
    "answer": "exclusively"
  },
  {
    "question": "The printers sold by Mitaka Innovations at a discounted price are of _________ quality to those sold elsewhere.\n",
    "choices": [
      "equivalencies",
      "equivalent",
      "equivalently",
      "equivalence"
    ],
    "answer": "equivalent"
  },
  {
    "question": "In addition to a salary, Inquell Insurance associates are paid a _________ based on a percentage of sales.\n",
    "choices": [
      "commission",
      "promotion",
      "donation",
      "permission"
    ],
    "answer": "commission"
  },
  {
    "question": "Aeronamic Footwear guarantees delivery within ten business days, _________ merchandise may arrive even more quickly.\n",
    "choices": [
      "beside",
      "if",
      "although",
      "whenever"
    ],
    "answer": "although"
  },
  {
    "question": "At the meeting on June 4, Ms. Srisati will _________ all misunderstandings surrounding the new phone system.\n",
    "choices": [
      "look out",
      "check in",
      "clear up",
      "take off"
    ],
    "answer": "clear up"
  },
  {
    "question": "With the new Web site enhancements, Hill Street Design customers will be able to view a _________ of recent purchases.\n",
    "choices": [
      "voucher",
      "coupon",
      "summary",
      "payment"
    ],
    "answer": "summary"
  },
  {
    "question": "The executive team of Trannelin Industries is determining _________ divisions will transfer to the West Coast next year.\n",
    "choices": [
      "any",
      "none",
      "each",
      "which"
    ],
    "answer": "which"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Fitzton Gallery has been the _________ promoter of the arts in Worthington, sponsoring numerous public events.\n",
    "choices": [
      "precise",
      "separate",
      "certain",
      "primary"
    ],
    "answer": "primary"
  },
  {
    "question": "The travel agent was able to obtain flights for the conference speakers _________ the last-minute request.\n",
    "choices": [
      "aboard",
      "despite",
      "aside",
      "beyond"
    ],
    "answer": "despite"
  },
  {
    "question": "Makiro Furniture customers can easily _________ helving units using only simple tools.\n",
    "choices": [
      "assemble",
      "assembled",
      "assembling",
      "assembles"
    ],
    "answer": "assemble"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mr. Zhao will _________ work on international accounts while Ms. Gutierrez is on leave.\n",
    "choices": [
      "temporarily",
      "comparatively",
      "nearly",
      "highly"
    ],
    "answer": "temporarily"
  },
  {
    "question": "According to the builder, the _________ of the main entrance will be completed in three weeks.\n",
    "choices": [
      "renovate",
      "renovates",
      "renovated",
      "renovation"
    ],
    "answer": "renovation"
  },
  {
    "question": "The park will remain open _________ the weather changes dramatically.\n",
    "choices": [
      "by",
      "unless",
      "common",
      "fast"
    ],
    "answer": "unless"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ms. Ansah's _________ report was excellent and needed no further revisions.\n",
    "choices": [
      "initial",
      "initially",
      "initiate",
      "initiates"
    ],
    "answer": "initial"
  },
  {
    "question": "Parkfield Fruit Bars have been made _________ added sugar since 1950.\n",
    "choices": [
      "between",
      "over",
      "without",
      "against"
    ],
    "answer": "without"
  },
  {
    "question": "The sales team has provided an _________ of customer preferences.\n",
    "choices": [
      "analyze",
      "analytical",
      "analysis",
      "analytically"
    ],
    "answer": "analysis"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ms. Sato is considered to be _________ talented for such a young painter.\n",
    "choices": [
      "indirectly",
      "rapidly",
      "carefully",
      "exceptionally"
    ],
    "answer": "exceptionally"
  },
  {
    "question": "Next month's town festival will feature a _________ author.\n",
    "choices": [
      "celebrate",
      "celebrates",
      "celebrated",
      "to celebrate"
    ],
    "answer": "celebrated"
  },
  {
    "question": "Car travel _________ the northern part of Willingboro will be difficult until the road repair projects are completed.\n",
    "choices": [
      "through",
      "under",
      "among",
      "upon"
    ],
    "answer": "through"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tonight's substitute _________ are listed on a separate piece of paper inserted in the theater program.\n",
    "choices": [
      "perform",
      "performers",
      "performing",
      "performance"
    ],
    "answer": "performers"
  },
  {
    "question": "All cakes were _________ to customers as expected on Saturday morning.\n",
    "choices": [
      "trusted",
      "delivered",
      "responded",
      "prevented"
    ],
    "answer": "delivered"
  },
  {
    "question": "Beginning on August 1, the _________ Sunday lunch menu will be offered on Saturdays as well.\n",
    "choices": [
      "popularity",
      "popularize",
      "popularly",
      "popular"
    ],
    "answer": "popular"
  },
  {
    "question": "Please let Ms. Choi know which staff members we will be sending as _________ to the engineering trade show.\n",
    "choices": [
      "techniques",
      "pieces",
      "debtors",
      "representatives"
    ],
    "answer": "representatives"
  },
  {
    "question": "New patients are advised to arrive fifteen minutes _________ their appointment time in order to complete the required paperwork.\n",
    "choices": [
      "into",
      "before",
      "beside",
      "within"
    ],
    "answer": "before"
  },
  {
    "question": "During his training period, Mr. Yun became _________ better at addressing the needs of customers.\n",
    "choices": [
      "progress",
      "progressed",
      "progressive",
      "progressively"
    ],
    "answer": "progressively"
  },
  {
    "question": "The flower-arranging workshop will be held in the large meeting room _________ over 30 people register by the May 1 deadline.\n",
    "choices": [
      "at",
      "if",
      "even",
      "instead"
    ],
    "answer": "if"
  },
  {
    "question": "Food display cases must be maintained at a _________ temperature to keep products fresh.\n",
    "choices": [
      "steady",
      "mature",
      "punctual",
      "curious"
    ],
    "answer": "steady"
  },
  {
    "question": "The staff does not know _________ mobile phone was left behind in the conference room.\n",
    "choices": [
      "neither",
      "whose",
      "nobody",
      "whoever"
    ],
    "answer": "whose"
  },
  {
    "question": "The first _________ of the Wilson Motors advertising campaign is to increase consumer awareness of the product.\n",
    "choices": [
      "plant",
      "sound",
      "goal",
      "room"
    ],
    "answer": "goal"
  },
  {
    "question": "The final cost _________ only slightly from the estimate we had received earlier in the year.\n",
    "choices": [
      "variety",
      "varied",
      "various",
      "variation"
    ],
    "answer": "varied"
  },
  {
    "question": "Since Mr. Park has worked in _________ accounting and marketing, he will bring much-needed experience to Mr. Lee's team.\n",
    "choices": [
      "both",
      "either",
      "whether",
      "although"
    ],
    "answer": "both"
  },
  {
    "question": "The visitor center at Wengle corporate headquarters is located _________ across from the main entrance to the complex.\n",
    "choices": [
      "direct",
      "direction",
      "directly",
      "directed"
    ],
    "answer": "directly"
  },
  {
    "question": "Washly Architects submitted a particularly _________ bid to design the new city office building.\n",
    "choices": [
      "imminent",
      "competitive",
      "abandoned",
      "heavier"
    ],
    "answer": "competitive"
  },
  {
    "question": "Farrier Auto Repair, _________ recently changed ownership, will expand its facilities considerably.\n",
    "choices": [
      "about",
      "which",
      "so that",
      "not only"
    ],
    "answer": "which"
  },
  {
    "question": "Our customized training sessions will show you how to make your business extremely _________.\n",
    "choices": [
      "alternate",
      "existent",
      "negotiated",
      "profitable"
    ],
    "answer": "profitable"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hotel guests who would like to _________ tomorrow's hike should contact the concierge, Ms. Jeong.\n",
    "choices": [
      "play with",
      "look through",
      "participate in",
      "adapt to"
    ],
    "answer": "participate in"
  },
  {
    "question": "Here at the Jeju Financial Group, we pride _________ on offering personalized guidance to satisfy clients' needs.\n",
    "choices": [
      "us",
      "our",
      "ourselves",
      "ours"
    ],
    "answer": "ourselves"
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ Ms. Lim finishes filing the receipts, she can start processing the new orders.\n",
    "choices": [
      "Further",
      "Also",
      "Once",
      "Rather"
    ],
    "answer": "Once"
  },
  {
    "question": "The conference center has recently become _________ with several local businesses.\n",
    "choices": [
      "affiliated",
      "crafted",
      "given",
      "shown"
    ],
    "answer": "affiliated"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ms. Choi will explain some of the _________ features of the new marketing software.\n",
    "choices": [
      "excite",
      "exciting",
      "excitedly",
      "excitement"
    ],
    "answer": "exciting"
  },
  {
    "question": "The admission _________ at the Altkirch Museum is €13 for nonmembers.\n",
    "choices": [
      "fee",
      "view",
      "curve",
      "doorway"
    ],
    "answer": "fee"
  },
  {
    "question": "Topscore Auto Parts uses modern inventory systems to replenish its stock _________.\n",
    "choices": [
      "continue",
      "continually",
      "continuation",
      "continual"
    ],
    "answer": "continually"
  },
  {
    "question": "TA new market will be located _________ Mason's Automobile Dealership and the Grace Theater.\n",
    "choices": [
      "down",
      "along",
      "across",
      "between"
    ],
    "answer": "between"
  },
  {
    "question": "Marketing has not yet decided _________ sandals to feature during Folberg Shoes' spring sale.\n",
    "choices": [
      "which",
      "that",
      "this",
      "those"
    ],
    "answer": "which"
  },
  {
    "question": "The principal of Wilson Oak Primary School _________ students as they arrived for their first day.\n",
    "choices": [
      "depended",
      "planned",
      "greeted",
      "wondered"
    ],
    "answer": "greeted"
  },
  {
    "question": "Zelwick Fashions will open its outlet in the suburbs _________ in the center of the city.\n",
    "choices": [
      "out of",
      "by far",
      "rather than",
      "less than"
    ],
    "answer": "rather than"
  },
  {
    "question": "Although some water from the storm entered the shop's basement, there was no _________.\n",
    "choices": [
      "recount",
      "damage",
      "caution",
      "bargain"
    ],
    "answer": "damage"
  },
  {
    "question": "Irons and ironing boards are available to Stennett Hotel guests upon _________.\n",
    "choices": [
      "request",
      "to request",
      "requested",
      "requester"
    ],
    "answer": "request"
  },
  {
    "question": "The finance department _________ reviews its quarterly statements carefully before they are released.\n",
    "choices": [
      "always",
      "ahead",
      "somewhat",
      "almost"
    ],
    "answer": "always"
  },
  {
    "question": "Though Bylertech's new video game is still being developed, some of its features have already been _________.\n",
    "choices": [
      "reveal",
      "revealed",
      "revealingly",
      "to reveal"
    ],
    "answer": "revealed"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ms. Takahashi's business trip will begin next Monday, _________ she leaves for Paris.\n",
    "choices": [
      "when",
      "despite",
      "such as",
      "as well as"
    ],
    "answer": "when"
  },
  {
    "question": "Because Mr. Lau has shown great _________ to his team, he was promoted to senior manager.\n",
    "choices": [
      "dedicate",
      "dedicated",
      "dedicating",
      "dedication"
    ],
    "answer": "dedication"
  },
  {
    "question": "Employees named to the innovations team should decide _________ themselves how to divide the work.\n",
    "choices": [
      "under",
      "among",
      "about",
      "from"
    ],
    "answer": "among"
  },
  {
    "question": "Leeds Accounting Group is seeking an administrative assistant _________ a variety of office tasks.\n",
    "choices": [
      "performs",
      "performed",
      "is performing",
      "to perform"
    ],
    "answer": "to perform"
  },
  {
    "question": "At Thimbleweeds, the prices of carpets are fixed, so customers do not have to worry about _________ costs.\n",
    "choices": [
      "recruitment",
      "added",
      "observed",
      "accommodation"
    ],
    "answer": "added"
  },
  {
    "question": "Based on her _________ approach to land-use management, Ms. Yoon was appointed to the Fairview Development Committee.\n",
    "choices": [
      "thinks",
      "thinker",
      "thoughtful",
      "thoughtfulness"
    ],
    "answer": "thoughtful"
  },
  {
    "question": "Westville Research employees have the leadership skills needed to _________ one or more assigned projects.\n",
    "choices": [
      "disturb",
      "involve",
      "reduce",
      "oversee"
    ],
    "answer": "oversee"
  },
  {
    "question": "Almost all of Samsoline's new fitness centers became _________ within the first year of business.\n",
    "choices": [
      "profit",
      "profited",
      "profitably",
      "profitable"
    ],
    "answer": "profitable"
  },
  {
    "question": "The _________ of sweet chocolate and salty toppings has made Kimmy's Coated Pretzels a sales success.\n",
    "choices": [
      "maintenance",
      "resistance",
      "understanding",
      "combination"
    ],
    "answer": "combination"
  },
  {
    "question": "Northland Spices _________ large amounts of paperwork when its new tracking software becomes operational.\n",
    "choices": [
      "will eliminate",
      "eliminating",
      "to eliminate",
      "has eliminated"
    ],
    "answer": "will eliminate"
  },
  {
    "question": "Springfield has completed renovations on the town hall to make it more _________ to all visitors.\n",
    "choices": [
      "accessible",
      "eager",
      "tactful",
      "abrupt"
    ],
    "answer": "accessible"
  },
  {
    "question": "Anberg Telecommunications sends customers monthly _________ Anberg Telecommunications sends customers monthly.\n",
    "choices": [
      "reminded",
      "reminds",
      "reminders",
      "to remind"
    ],
    "answer": "reminders"
  },
  {
    "question": "The city has _________ increased the budget to better support community programs.\n",
    "choices": [
      "substantially",
      "nearly",
      "accidentally",
      "tightly"
    ],
    "answer": "substantially"
  },
  {
    "question": "New patients should arrive early _________ that they have time to fill out the required paperwork.\n",
    "choices": [
      "so",
      "because",
      "for",
      "even"
    ],
    "answer": "so"
  },
  {
    "question": "BD's Car Services may have to _________ its hiring policy in light of the worker shortage.\n",
    "choices": [
      "filter",
      "locate",
      "reconsider",
      "see"
    ],
    "answer": "reconsider"
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ volunteers to organize the retirement party for Ms. Chung will need to invite her family.\n",
    "choices": [
      "Whom",
      "When",
      "Whose",
      "Whoever"
    ],
    "answer": "Whoever"
  },
  {
    "question": "The marine-biology building will be named after Dr. Mellisa Vasquez, who has conducted _________ research on dolphins.\n",
    "choices": [
      "sociable",
      "groundbreaking",
      "amused",
      "cluttered"
    ],
    "answer": "groundbreaking"
  },
  {
    "question": "To meet increased customer demand just before the holiday, salesclerks had to work _________ more hours than usual.\n",
    "choices": [
      "signify",
      "signified",
      "significant",
      "significantly"
    ],
    "answer": "significantly"
  },
  {
    "question": "Highlake Toys sends a confirmation message to customers _________ they place an order online.\n",
    "choices": [
      "during",
      "in particular",
      "along with",
      "as soon as"
    ],
    "answer": "as soon as"
  },
  {
    "question": "You must carry your driver's license _________ employee identification card with you when you drive a company-owned car.\n",
    "choices": [
      "and",
      "but",
      "either",
      "which"
    ],
    "answer": "and"
  },
  {
    "question": "Businesses on Ellory Avenue _________ early yesterday to allow work crews to repave the street.\n",
    "choices": [
      "are closed",
      "to close",
      "closing",
      "closed"
    ],
    "answer": "closed"
  },
  {
    "question": "J & R Marketing won an award for its series of radio _________ promoting a new line of sports equipment.\n",
    "choices": [
      "sponsors",
      "advertisements",
      "posters",
      "announcers"
    ],
    "answer": "advertisements"
  },
  {
    "question": "Associates who are traveling to Pusan for the sales conference will have to make _________ own travel arrangements.\n",
    "choices": [
      "themselves",
      "they",
      "them",
      "their"
    ],
    "answer": "their"
  },
  {
    "question": "Event organizers _________ an increase in the number of vendors at this year's art festival.\n",
    "choices": [
      "anticipate",
      "anticipates",
      "anticipating",
      "to anticipate"
    ],
    "answer": "anticipate"
  },
  {
    "question": "Enclosed is a _________ updated copy of my résumé, which includes my more recent managerial experience.\n",
    "choices": [
      "newly",
      "too",
      "likely",
      "fast"
    ],
    "answer": "newly"
  },
  {
    "question": "Earlier today, IGY Corporation released a _________ confirming its plans for expansion in South America.\n",
    "choices": [
      "state",
      "stating",
      "statement",
      "stated"
    ],
    "answer": "statement"
  },
  {
    "question": "Please remember to obtain your new keys before the locks to the office doors are changed _________ Tuesday.\n",
    "choices": [
      "yet",
      "last",
      "almost",
      "on"
    ],
    "answer": "on"
  },
  {
    "question": "A consumer report has revealed that less expensive laundry detergents can be _________ as effective as the more expensive products.\n",
    "choices": [
      "soon",
      "just",
      "very",
      "so"
    ],
    "answer": "just"
  },
  {
    "question": "The board of directors at Relvan Computing _________ meets once a month.\n",
    "choices": [
      "general",
      "generalize",
      "generally",
      "generalized"
    ],
    "answer": "generally"
  },
  {
    "question": "Basic _________ for the magazine editor position include a journalism degree and knowledge of publishing software.\n",
    "choices": [
      "qualifying",
      "qualifications",
      "qualifies",
      "qualify"
    ],
    "answer": "qualifications"
  },
  {
    "question": "The construction on Highway 12 is expected to continue _________ next month.\n",
    "choices": [
      "until",
      "across",
      "down",
      "onto"
    ],
    "answer": "until"
  },
  {
    "question": "Interns at Travan Industries received a one-day _________ to acquaint them with the facility and company procedures.\n",
    "choices": [
      "direction",
      "version",
      "orientation",
      "option"
    ],
    "answer": "orientation"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mr. Woo declined to _________ on rumors that he is planning to retire.\n",
    "choices": [
      "commenting",
      "commentary",
      "comment",
      "comments"
    ],
    "answer": "comment"
  },
  {
    "question": "Anyone who knows a _________ network administrator should contact Wendy Liu in accounting.\n",
    "choices": [
      "certify",
      "to certify",
      "certified",
      "certifies"
    ],
    "answer": "certified"
  },
  {
    "question": "Only applicants who meet all the requirements for the position will be _________ to an interview with the hiring committee.\n",
    "choices": [
      "invited",
      "attended",
      "judged",
      "continued"
    ],
    "answer": "invited"
  },
  {
    "question": "The workers from Sanders Plumbing have earned a reputation for _________ and courteous service.\n",
    "choices": [
      "possible",
      "numerous",
      "previous",
      "reliable"
    ],
    "answer": "reliable"
  },
  {
    "question": "In response to favorable customer feedback, Snowy Peak Travel has announced a one-month _________ of its special Skyline Tour offer.\n",
    "choices": [
      "extension",
      "extend",
      "extensive",
      "extended"
    ],
    "answer": "extension"
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketing consultant for the Trepin Group _________ included incorrect data on the customer survey report.\n",
    "choices": [
      "mistakenly",
      "mistake",
      "to mistake",
      "mistaking"
    ],
    "answer": "mistakenly"
  },
  {
    "question": "Guests are required to pay their telephone charges when they _________ at the hotel reception desk.\n",
    "choices": [
      "bring",
      "check out",
      "remove",
      "drop off"
    ],
    "answer": "check out"
  },
  {
    "question": "Neumann Shoe Company is moving from its _________ location in Hamburg to a more modern facility in Reinbek.\n",
    "choices": [
      "present",
      "timely",
      "widespread",
      "assorted"
    ],
    "answer": "present"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tim O'Donnell's years of experience and _________ make him an excellent choice for the position of marketing director.\n",
    "choices": [
      "professionalism",
      "professional",
      "professionally",
      "professionalize"
    ],
    "answer": "professionalism"
  },
  {
    "question": "Any equipment that does not arrive in perfect _________ may be returned to QMZ Electronics free of charge.\n",
    "choices": [
      "development",
      "condition",
      "problem",
      "situation"
    ],
    "answer": "condition"
  },
  {
    "question": "Studies have shown that travelers benefit financially _________ being able to make their own flight and hotel reservations.\n",
    "choices": [
      "for",
      "from",
      "plus",
      "about"
    ],
    "answer": "from"
  },
  {
    "question": "While the preliminary research is favorable, it may take years for Bogor Pharmaceuticals to develop _________ evidence of the drug's effectiveness.\n",
    "choices": [
      "conclusion",
      "concludes",
      "conclusive",
      "conclude"
    ],
    "answer": "conclusive"
  },
  {
    "question": "The specialists at Grayson Office Interiors _________ cubicles and other workstations to suit the needs of almost any type of business.\n",
    "choices": [
      "recline",
      "invest",
      "satisfy",
      "design"
    ],
    "answer": "design"
  },
  {
    "question": "Construction on a new wing at the Markunas Museum _________ as soon as additional funding has been arranged.\n",
    "choices": [
      "has been resumed",
      "will resume",
      "was resumed",
      "to be resuming"
    ],
    "answer": "will resume"
  },
  {
    "question": "Drade Technologies has responded _________ to our proposal for its new advertising campaign.\n",
    "choices": [
      "favorable",
      "favorite",
      "favorably",
      "favoring"
    ],
    "answer": "favorably"
  },
  {
    "question": "Angus Wienholt's seminar provides a _________ approach to starting a business using resources that are widely available.\n",
    "choices": [
      "sizable",
      "constant",
      "variety",
      "practical"
    ],
    "answer": "practical"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Oliveira Dining Guide, an online directory of restaurants, is _________ by cuisine type, price range, and location.\n",
    "choices": [
      "search",
      "searcher",
      "searches",
      "searchable"
    ],
    "answer": "searchable"
  },
  {
    "question": "Routine inspections are conducted at the Haldren Paper factory to ensure that all equipment is functioning _________.\n",
    "choices": [
      "properly",
      "officially",
      "literally",
      "rightfully"
    ],
    "answer": "properly"
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ should impress passengers most is the comfort of the reupholstered seating at Liverpool Regional Airport.\n",
    "choices": [
      "Who",
      "What",
      "When",
      "Where"
    ],
    "answer": "What"
  },
  {
    "question": "Akira Nakayama _________ delay the filming of his documentary in the rainforest when his equipment did not arrive on schedule.\n",
    "choices": [
      "has to",
      "will have to",
      "having to",
      "had to"
    ],
    "answer": "had to"
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ you return after the rental counter closes for the evening, place your vehicle's keys in the night return slot.\n",
    "choices": [
      "Because of",
      "Prior to",
      "In the event that",
      "As a consequence"
    ],
    "answer": "In the event that"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ever since book critic Martha Taybe praised Reinaldo Da Silva's The Flag Bearer, _________ for it has skyrocketed.\n",
    "choices": [
      "structure",
      "effort",
      "demand",
      "vision"
    ],
    "answer": "demand"
  },
  {
    "question": "Nabhi Verma, who holds degrees in both architecture and engineering, has a range of technical abilities _________ that of his peers.\n",
    "choices": [
      "too much",
      "moreover",
      "even more",
      "beyond"
    ],
    "answer": "beyond"
  },
  {
    "question": "Artists at the Zadone Gallery are able to create reproductions of famous paintings that are _________ authentic looking.\n",
    "choices": [
      "remark",
      "remarkably",
      "remarkable",
      "remarkableness"
    ],
    "answer": "remarkably"
  },
  {
    "question": "Clarkson Library will be closed for renovations from May 3 to July 15, _________ which time the collection will not be open to the public.\n",
    "choices": [
      "with",
      "while",
      "during",
      "between"
    ],
    "answer": "during"
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ just six months ago, Finson's Grill has quickly become one of the most popular restaurants in Delton.\n",
    "choices": [
      "Opened",
      "To open",
      "Been opened",
      "Had been opening"
    ],
    "answer": "Opened"
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ analysts' predictions, McKnight Electronic engineers were able to create a battery capable of lasting twice as long as previous models.\n",
    "choices": [
      "Nevertheless",
      "Provided that",
      "Except",
      "Contrary to"
    ],
    "answer": "Contrary to"
  },
  {
    "question": "Williamstown Borough Bikes is open on weekdays _________ 10 A.M. to 5 P.M.\n",
    "choices": [
      "from",
      "since",
      "by",
      "until"
    ],
    "answer": "from"
  },
  {
    "question": "All Dokgo Design employees should update _________ timesheets daily.\n",
    "choices": [
      "theirs",
      "them",
      "their",
      "they"
    ],
    "answer": "their"
  },
  {
    "question": "A street map _________ a travel guide are available on the city's official Web site.\n",
    "choices": [
      "So",
      "but",
      "and",
      "nor"
    ],
    "answer": "and"
  },
  {
    "question": "Factory _________ have helped Zubiri Footwear to improve the design of its popular Airwing running shoe.\n",
    "choices": [
      "test",
      "tests",
      "tested",
      "testing"
    ],
    "answer": "tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "The mayor of Pipersville has not _________ reviewed the proposal to expand Grey Park.\n",
    "choices": [
      "yet",
      "soon",
      "very",
      "after"
    ],
    "answer": "yet"
  },
  {
    "question": "Please _________ the owner's manual before using your Kivi Craft oven for the first time.\n",
    "choices": [
      "consulting",
      "consulted",
      "consults",
      "consult"
    ],
    "answer": "consult"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tonight's speech will be followed _________ by a reception for Bluebonnet Travel Services' new vice president.\n",
    "choices": [
      "often",
      "directly",
      "already",
      "lately"
    ],
    "answer": "directly"
  },
  {
    "question": "Caritas Kitchen Accessories is best known for its line of _________ coffeemakers.\n",
    "choices": [
      "depends",
      "depended",
      "depending",
      "dependable"
    ],
    "answer": "dependable"
  },
  {
    "question": "Comments or suggestions concerning our dining service _________ welcome.\n",
    "choices": [
      "is",
      "are",
      "to be",
      "being"
    ],
    "answer": "are"
  },
  {
    "question": "Estway Theater's advertising strategy has been to rely _________ on digital media.\n",
    "choices": [
      "increase",
      "increases",
      "increasing",
      "increasingly"
    ],
    "answer": "increasingly"
  },
  {
    "question": "To adjust the volume of the Sharpe Sound microphone, _________ the knob to the left or right.\n",
    "choices": [
      "choose",
      "listen",
      "turn",
      "let"
    ],
    "answer": "turn"
  },
  {
    "question": "With its unusual blend of Korean and Mexican cuisines, La Cantina Han offers the most _________ dining experience in the city.\n",
    "choices": [
      "surprise",
      "surprised",
      "surprises",
      "surprising"
    ],
    "answer": "surprising"
  },
  {
    "question": "To protect the camera lens, be sure to reattach the lens cover _________ returning the camera to its case.\n",
    "choices": [
      "when",
      "what",
      "whether",
      "why"
    ],
    "answer": "when"
  },
  {
    "question": "The board of directors will vote at today's meeting on the _________ to merge with Fray Publishing.\n",
    "choices": [
      "plan",
      "summary",
      "book",
      "list"
    ],
    "answer": "plan"
  },
  {
    "question": "So far this quarter, regional sales of compact cars have surpassed industry analysts’ _________.\n",
    "choices": [
      "predicts",
      "predicted",
      "predictions",
      "predictable"
    ],
    "answer": "predictions"
  },
  {
    "question": "Any mechanir ai maunction of exercise _________ should be reported to the gym manager without delay.\n",
    "choices": [
      "features",
      "equipment",
      "results",
      "routine"
    ],
    "answer": "equipment"
  },
  {
    "question": "Leroy-Bontemps researched consumer _________ around the nation as part of the development of its low-calorie beverage products.\n",
    "choices": [
      "preferred",
      "preferable",
      "preferences",
      "preferring"
    ],
    "answer": "preferences"
  },
  {
    "question": "For one week _________, Leah's Boutique is offering a 20 percent discount on all summer clothing items.\n",
    "choices": [
      "ever",
      "off",
      "single",
      "only"
    ],
    "answer": "only"
  },
  {
    "question": "A marketing survey can help a company to identify potential customers _________ analyze its business competitors.\n",
    "choices": [
      "as well as",
      "instead",
      "while",
      "for example"
    ],
    "answer": "as well as"
  },
  {
    "question": "Redbury Town Library has received nearly €5,000 in contributions _________ the last twelve months.\n",
    "choices": [
      "above",
      "behind",
      "over",
      "along"
    ],
    "answer": "over"
  },
  {
    "question": "A new lighting system has been installed in the administrative offices, _________ the older, less efficient one.\n",
    "choices": [
      "replacing",
      "comparing",
      "brightening",
      "repairing"
    ],
    "answer": "replacing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Dr. Patel is considered to be one of today's most influential economic policy analysts by _________ in the field.\n",
    "choices": [
      "other",
      "others",
      "itself",
      "themselves"
    ],
    "answer": "others"
  },
  {
    "question": "The traffic patterns described in the report pertain _________ to automobile drivers and do not apply to motorcyclists.\n",
    "choices": [
      "exclusively",
      "exclusive",
      "exclusion",
      "excluded"
    ],
    "answer": "exclusively"
  },
  {
    "question": "Event planners noted that attendance at last night's awards ceremony was discouragingly _________.\n",
    "choices": [
      "empty",
      "low",
      "lesser",
      "few"
    ],
    "answer": "low"
  },
  {
    "question": "Parnpradub Graphic Design requires that employees possess advanced technical _________, including proficiency in numerous computer programs.\n",
    "choices": [
      "expert",
      "experts",
      "expertly",
      "expertise"
    ],
    "answer": "expertise"
  },
  {
    "question": "Articles submitted for punitation in the Sinchon Review should be no more than ten pages _________ length.\n",
    "choices": [
      "under",
      "in",
      "inside",
      "at"
    ],
    "answer": "in"
  },
  {
    "question": "The position of shipping clerk requires _________ lifting of packages weighing over twenty kilograms.\n",
    "choices": [
      "repeats",
      "repeated",
      "repeatedly",
      "will repeat"
    ],
    "answer": "repeated"
  },
  {
    "question": "In an effort to compete on a global _________, Kasper-Levi is doubling its marketing budget in Asia.\n",
    "choices": [
      "progress",
      "scale",
      "locale",
      "series"
    ],
    "answer": "scale"
  },
  {
    "question": "The screen of the latest Carrack XT computer monitor is 15 percent larger than _________ of the previous model.\n",
    "choices": [
      "which",
      "those",
      "whose",
      "that"
    ],
    "answer": "that"
  },
  {
    "question": "The delegation will depart from the embassy at 9 A.M. and _________ to the airport by the Minister of Sports.\n",
    "choices": [
      "will accompany",
      "accompanied",
      "will be accompanied",
      "being accompanied"
    ],
    "answer": "will be accompanied"
  },
  {
    "question": "In addition to rustic charm and easy access to the beach, the hotel _________ spectacular views of the ocean.\n",
    "choices": [
      "offers",
      "registers",
      "reserves",
      "bounds"
    ],
    "answer": "offers"
  },
  {
    "question": "When Dr. Bennett's flight was canceled, she had to catch a train in order to arrive _________ for her appointment.\n",
    "choices": [
      "more punctual",
      "punctuality",
      "punctual",
      "punctually"
    ],
    "answer": "punctually"
  },
  {
    "question": "By the end of the course of study, Gant College students are expected to have mastered the skills _________ to their chosen fields.\n",
    "choices": [
      "specific",
      "narrow",
      "detailed",
      "exacting"
    ],
    "answer": "specific"
  },
  {
    "question": "Its electronic rice cooker proved so _________ with consumers that Namgung Technik had to accelerate production of the item.\n",
    "choices": [
      "popularize",
      "popularity",
      "popular",
      "popularly"
    ],
    "answer": "popular"
  },
  {
    "question": "Shinoda Med, Inc., strives to be at the _________ of advancements in dental health technology.\n",
    "choices": [
      "headline",
      "highlight",
      "guidepost",
      "forefront"
    ],
    "answer": "forefront"
  },
  {
    "question": "Entertainment industry reporters speculated that Janggok Media would release its next film by year's end, but the company decided to do _________.\n",
    "choices": [
      "after all",
      "on the whole",
      "otherwise",
      "accordingly"
    ],
    "answer": "otherwise"
  },
  {
    "question": "By _________ the furniture shipping process, we can lower expenses and cut the delivery time in half.\n",
    "choices": [
      "outpacing",
      "streamlining",
      "persevering",
      "forestalling"
    ],
    "answer": "streamlining"
  },
  {
    "question": "Executive Director Rajiv Kutty has complied with shareholders’ requests that he _________ quality control procedures at Srinivisan Foods facilities.\n",
    "choices": [
      "review",
      "was reviewing",
      "be reviewed",
      "reviewed"
    ],
    "answer": "review"
  },
  {
    "question": "With three decades of university administration experience, Professor Wallis Is a _________ choice to be the leader of the campus planning committee.\n",
    "choices": [
      "total",
      "precise",
      "logical",
      "reliant"
    ],
    "answer": "logical"
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ delays in obtaining the proper construction permits, renovation of the civic center will not resume until Monday.\n",
    "choices": [
      "Ahead of",
      "Negotiable",
      "Owing to",
      "Regrettable"
    ],
    "answer": "Owing to"
  },
  {
    "question": "Next year Khosun Industries will _________ several employees to work in the new factory in Kuala Lumpur.\n",
    "choices": [
      "sent",
      "send",
      "sends",
      "sending"
    ],
    "answer": "send"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Bernier Company's financial reports are typically published in _________ English and French.\n",
    "choices": [
      "neither",
      "yet",
      "so",
      "both"
    ],
    "answer": "both"
  },
  {
    "question": "Dr. Vargas will soon retire, ending _________ distinguished 30-year career as a research scientist with Gillan Laboratories.\n",
    "choices": [
      "she",
      "hers",
      "her",
      "herself"
    ],
    "answer": "her"
  },
  {
    "question": "The route to Sandy Shores Inn is _________ marked from exit 262 on the coastal highway.\n",
    "choices": [
      "clearly",
      "freely",
      "deeply",
      "sharply"
    ],
    "answer": "clearly"
  },
  {
    "question": "A _________ from Jensen-Colmes Corporation will be happy to meet with prospective job applicants at the Westborough Job Fair.\n",
    "choices": [
      "represent",
      "representing",
      "representative",
      "representation"
    ],
    "answer": "representative"
  },
  {
    "question": "Please review the new safety procedures and _________ any questions to Mr. Bae at extension 2528.\n",
    "choices": [
      "inquire",
      "direct",
      "expect",
      "prepare"
    ],
    "answer": "direct"
  },
  {
    "question": "Visitors to the library are asked to speak _________ and keep conversations brief when in the main reading room.\n",
    "choices": [
      "quiet",
      "quietly",
      "quietest",
      "quietness"
    ],
    "answer": "quietly"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Milltown Cinema's outdoor café will be closed _________ the winter months.\n",
    "choices": [
      "about",
      "out of",
      "next to",
      "during"
    ],
    "answer": "during"
  },
  {
    "question": "Daily guided tours of the warehouse _________ at 10:00 A.M. in the reception area on the first floor.\n",
    "choices": [
      "begin",
      "begins",
      "to begin",
      "beginning"
    ],
    "answer": "begin"
  },
  {
    "question": "Telephone-conferencing equipment is _________ available in every meeting room in the Judson Building.\n",
    "choices": [
      "once",
      "now",
      "right",
      "far"
    ],
    "answer": "now"
  },
  {
    "question": "Saturday's clearance sale will reduce old stock and make room for next season's products, _________ will arrive very soon.\n",
    "choices": [
      "when",
      "what",
      "where",
      "which"
    ],
    "answer": "which"
  },
  {
    "question": "Visitors must sign in at the security desk and provide photo identification in order to _________ visitor passes.\n",
    "choices": [
      "obtain",
      "design",
      "require",
      "involve"
    ],
    "answer": "obtain"
  },
  {
    "question": "As part of its business expansion _________, Ausgaard Automobiles plans to launch a line of small utility trucks.\n",
    "choices": [
      "strategize",
      "strategic",
      "strategy",
      "strategically"
    ],
    "answer": "strategy"
  },
  {
    "question": "The department-wide changes suggested _________ Ms. Juntasa received unanimous approval from company management.\n",
    "choices": [
      "in",
      "of",
      "by",
      "as"
    ],
    "answer": "by"
  },
  {
    "question": "Candidates for positions at Pereira Consulting should answer the questions on the application form as _________ as possible.\n",
    "choices": [
      "accurate",
      "accuracy",
      "accuracies",
      "accurately"
    ],
    "answer": "accurately"
  },
  {
    "question": "Marden Manufacturing, Inc., is hiring temporary workers to address the present _________ for greater personnel resources.\n",
    "choices": [
      "measure",
      "denial",
      "demand",
      "claim"
    ],
    "answer": "demand"
  },
  {
    "question": "Crown Corporation has been the nation's _________ commercial supplier of fabric dyes for over 25 years.\n",
    "choices": [
      "leads",
      "leader",
      "to lead",
      "leading"
    ],
    "answer": "leading"
  },
  {
    "question": "The community swimming pool is not to be used at any time _________ a trained lifeguard is on duty.\n",
    "choices": [
      "in fact",
      "unless",
      "in case",
      "otherwise"
    ],
    "answer": "unless"
  },
  {
    "question": "The exhibition of German sculpture will be on _________ for the next twelve weeks at the Richter Art Museum.\n",
    "choices": [
      "display",
      "appearance",
      "arrangement",
      "survey"
    ],
    "answer": "display"
  },
  {
    "question": "Employees must receive _________ approval for any travel that will be reimbursed by the company.\n",
    "choices": [
      "close",
      "past",
      "prior",
      "late"
    ],
    "answer": "prior"
  },
  {
    "question": "Most of the new houses for sale on Seegers Island are _________ priced and in excellent condition.\n",
    "choices": [
      "moderate",
      "moderated",
      "moderately",
      "moderation"
    ],
    "answer": "moderately"
  },
  {
    "question": "All members of the sales team are grateful for Michael Dreyman's substantial _________ to the project over the last six months.\n",
    "choices": [
      "assurance",
      "dependence",
      "obligations",
      "contributions"
    ],
    "answer": "contributions"
  },
  {
    "question": "Researchers at Firmatek Synthetics are working on a new material that will be twice as _________ as ordinary concrete.\n",
    "choices": [
      "durably",
      "durable",
      "durability",
      "durableness"
    ],
    "answer": "durable"
  },
  {
    "question": "Dr. Knudsen's patient base has grown so rapidly that he must _________ with another physician.\n",
    "choices": [
      "partner",
      "afford",
      "hire",
      "conform"
    ],
    "answer": "partner"
  },
  {
    "question": "The content on the Aspero Designs Web site is protected by copyright law and may not be reproduced _________ the company's written consent.\n",
    "choices": [
      "behind",
      "without",
      "except",
      "before"
    ],
    "answer": "without"
  },
  {
    "question": "Dr. Hemana and Dr. Wareham, the joint recipients of the Cobalt Research Prize, have known _________ since they were university students in Auckland.\n",
    "choices": [
      "other one",
      "another one",
      "any other",
      "each other"
    ],
    "answer": "each other"
  },
  {
    "question": "Customers who purchase concert tickets will be charged a service fee _________ they pay by cash or by credit card.\n",
    "choices": [
      "whether",
      "either",
      "even",
      "despite"
    ],
    "answer": "whether"
  },
  {
    "question": "In addition to fine dining, the elegant Ipswich Inn provides every amenity _________ for small or large business meetings.\n",
    "choices": [
      "necessity",
      "necessitate",
      "necessary",
      "necessarily"
    ],
    "answer": "necessary"
  },
  {
    "question": "As head of Human Resources, Rachel Ashton will inform _________ employees of job openings before advertising the positions on the Internet.\n",
    "choices": [
      "allowable",
      "entire",
      "permissive",
      "current"
    ],
    "answer": "current"
  },
  {
    "question": "The library at the Kane-Clark Institute contains numerous items _________ the history of the renowned philanthropic organization.\n",
    "choices": [
      "document",
      "documents",
      "documentary",
      "documenting"
    ],
    "answer": "documenting"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mr. Takei attended one business conference in April and plans to attend two more conferences _________ in the year.\n",
    "choices": [
      "then",
      "later",
      "long",
      "ever"
    ],
    "answer": "later"
  },
  {
    "question": "Whitcomb Hospital's new efficiency program aims to reduce the workload of hospital employees while improving patient _________.\n",
    "choices": [
      "care",
      "cared",
      "careful",
      "carefully"
    ],
    "answer": "care"
  },
  {
    "question": "This afternoon's flights to Barcelona, London, and Rome have all been delayed _________ inclement weather in the destination cities.\n",
    "choices": [
      "as for",
      "due to",
      "now that",
      "only if"
    ],
    "answer": "due to"
  },
  {
    "question": "To save time and costs, Alberta Industries recommends that any associates who travel for business _________ the amount of luggage they carry.\n",
    "choices": [
      "minimize",
      "to minimize",
      "have minimized",
      "minimizing"
    ],
    "answer": "minimize"
  },
  {
    "question": "Patrons who arrive at the theater _________ the show has begun will not be seated until the intermission.\n",
    "choices": [
      "wherever",
      "into",
      "along",
      "after"
    ],
    "answer": "after"
  },
  {
    "question": "Parking is prohibited in areas marked for emergency use, and drivers who park their vehicles in these zones are _________ to substantial fines.\n",
    "choices": [
      "subject",
      "subjecting",
      "subjection",
      "subjections"
    ],
    "answer": "subject"
  },
  {
    "question": "According to the proposal, a large block of rooms in the east wing of the new building will be _________ for storage.\n",
    "choices": [
      "designated",
      "detained",
      "reciprocated",
      "signified"
    ],
    "answer": "designated"
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ of homegrown and organic fruits and vegetables, as well as handmade crafts and jewelry, are available for purchase at the Springdale community market.\n",
    "choices": [
      "Varies",
      "Variant",
      "Varieties",
      "Various"
    ],
    "answer": "Varieties"
  },
  {
    "question": "The research and development division at Spiridon Biometrics has improved the quality and scope of its products under Ms. Chang's _________.\n",
    "choices": [
      "disposal",
      "direction",
      "prominence",
      "capacity"
    ],
    "answer": "direction"
  },
  {
    "question": "Customers concerned about _________ utility rate increases will be given the option of prepaying for three months of service at today's rate.\n",
    "choices": [
      "considerate",
      "instructive",
      "probable",
      "expended"
    ],
    "answer": "probable"
  },
  {
    "question": "The new-product development meeting will be held either in Room 402 _________ in Room 501.\n",
    "choices": [
      "or",
      "and",
      "not",
      "but"
    ],
    "answer": "or"
  },
  {
    "question": "The restaurant will _________ for two days later this month for remodeling.\n",
    "choices": [
      "hold",
      "build",
      "close",
      "invite"
    ],
    "answer": "close"
  },
  {
    "question": "The advertising budget is divided _________ among the three divisions in the marketing department.\n",
    "choices": [
      "equal",
      "equals",
      "equality",
      "equally"
    ],
    "answer": "equally"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mr. Fullham's investments in small start-up companies have doubled _________ value in just over five years.\n",
    "choices": [
      "they",
      "their",
      "them",
      "themselves"
    ],
    "answer": "their"
  },
  {
    "question": "Printer cartridges can be found in the supply cabinet _________ the file folders.\n",
    "choices": [
      "at",
      "from",
      "with",
      "along"
    ],
    "answer": "with"
  },
  {
    "question": "Solar power is being heavily promoted as a clean and _________ source of energy.\n",
    "choices": [
      "renew",
      "renews",
      "renewal",
      "renewable"
    ],
    "answer": "renewable"
  },
  {
    "question": "Registrations for the next lecture series must be _________ by the end of this week.\n",
    "choices": [
      "belonged",
      "practiced",
      "received",
      "arrived"
    ],
    "answer": "received"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mr. Montrose's _________ in his job search has resulted in employment offers from three companies.\n",
    "choices": [
      "persist",
      "persisted",
      "persistently",
      "persistence"
    ],
    "answer": "persistence"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ms. Vialobos has reported that the new mobile telephones are the lightest _________ to be purchased by the department.\n",
    "choices": [
      "ever",
      "before",
      "quite",
      "well"
    ],
    "answer": "ever"
  },
  {
    "question": "Orders _________ the weight limit are subject to additional shipping fees.\n",
    "choices": [
      "exceed",
      "exceeded",
      "exceeding",
      "excessive"
    ],
    "answer": "exceeding"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mr. Wong will travel to the management seminar in Singapore on _________.\n",
    "choices": [
      "he",
      "himself",
      "him",
      "his own"
    ],
    "answer": "his own"
  },
  {
    "question": "According to an informal survey, the sales goal set by the management team seems _________ to most of the staff.\n",
    "choices": [
      "realist",
      "realism",
      "realistic",
      "realistically"
    ],
    "answer": "realistic"
  },
  {
    "question": "Because the packaging machines _________ break down on the assembly line, factory officials have decided to replace them.\n",
    "choices": [
      "repeat",
      "repeatedly",
      "repeated",
      "repetition"
    ],
    "answer": "repeatedly"
  },
  {
    "question": "Workers are _________ against entering the laboratory without protective clothing and masks.\n",
    "choices": [
      "cautious",
      "caution",
      "cautiously",
      "cautioned"
    ],
    "answer": "cautioned"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ms. Gupta wishes to _________ the terms of her employment contract before signing it.\n",
    "choices": [
      "deprive",
      "respond",
      "modify",
      "assure"
    ],
    "answer": "modify"
  },
  {
    "question": "Highway 140 is not _________ by Exit 2A due to road construction.\n",
    "choices": [
      "occupied",
      "accessible",
      "exposed",
      "possible"
    ],
    "answer": "accessible"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mr. Thomas and Ms. Vasquez _________ to work together on the market research project.\n",
    "choices": [
      "assigned",
      "assigning",
      "will assign",
      "have been assigned"
    ],
    "answer": "have been assigned"
  },
  {
    "question": "Because of its _________ for outstanding customer service, Mei's Hair Salon is the most popular business of its kind in the area.\n",
    "choices": [
      "approval",
      "estimation",
      "probability",
      "reputation"
    ],
    "answer": "reputation"
  },
  {
    "question": "Market researchers reported that customers were most impressed _________ the Vestra Coffeemaker's delayed-start function.\n",
    "choices": [
      "by",
      "beyond",
      "for",
      "since"
    ],
    "answer": "by"
  },
  {
    "question": "By the time the magazine article on home security devices _________ on the newsstands, the pricing information was already outdated.\n",
    "choices": [
      "appears",
      "appeared",
      "will appear",
      "appearing"
    ],
    "answer": "appeared"
  },
  {
    "question": "After December 13 customers will be asked to place their orders online _________ use the mail-order form.\n",
    "choices": [
      "so as",
      "in case",
      "rather than",
      "provided that"
    ],
    "answer": "rather than"
  },
  {
    "question": "Bylar Corporate Furnishings is the _________ office-furniture vendor for several of the area's largest corporations.\n",
    "choices": [
      "prefer",
      "preferred",
      "preference",
      "preferential"
    ],
    "answer": "preferred"
  },
  {
    "question": "Science Gadgets, Inc., supports every product it sells _________ and will gladly offer a refund for any purchase a customer is dissatisfied with.\n",
    "choices": [
      "conclusively",
      "factually",
      "unconditionally",
      "steadily"
    ],
    "answer": "unconditionally"
  },
  {
    "question": "A quarterly survey _________ by Car Trade magazine shows that customers prefer fuel-efficiency over size or price when purchasing a new automobile.\n",
    "choices": [
      "performed",
      "performs",
      "had performed",
      "to perform"
    ],
    "answer": "performed"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ferrelli Steel has _________ in talks with Montag Fabrics to purchase part of its manufacturing business.\n",
    "choices": [
      "involved",
      "engaged",
      "demonstrated",
      "maintained"
    ],
    "answer": "engaged"
  },
  {
    "question": "Patent laws guarantee that Halperin Engineering, Inc., has _________  rights to the technology it developed for robotic surgical devices.\n",
    "choices": [
      "responsible",
      "feasible",
      "manufactured",
      "exclusive"
    ],
    "answer": "exclusive"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Culver Award is given annually to an individual or organization that demonstrates _________  in the field of public transportation.\n",
    "choices": [
      "innovate",
      "innovation",
      "innovative",
      "innovatively"
    ],
    "answer": "innovation"
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ its main competitor, the ergonomic chair offered by Well Designs is lightweight and comes in a variety of colors.\n",
    "choices": [
      "In contrast to",
      "By way of",
      "Instead of",
      "So as"
    ],
    "answer": "In contrast to"
  },
  {
    "question": "Several _________ have been made to the layout of Banham Library's Web site.\n",
    "choices": [
      "revisions",
      "processes",
      "considerations",
      "concepts"
    ],
    "answer": "revisions"
  },
  {
    "question": "The parks and recreation department is meeting to discuss what _________ the extensive sewer work will have for the outdoor summer concert series in Evergreen Park.\n",
    "choices": [
      "implicated",
      "implicate",
      "implications",
      "implicating"
    ],
    "answer": "implications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Guests are asked to register at the front desk _________ entering the main lobby.\n",
    "choices": [
      "upon",
      "about",
      "in order to",
      "whoever"
    ],
    "answer": "upon"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mr. Tomita was pleased that Ms. Arai was _________ to adjust her schedule at the last minute in order to revise the financial report.\n",
    "choices": [
      "busy",
      "willing",
      "changed",
      "timely"
    ],
    "answer": "willing"
  },
  {
    "question": "There is a _________ to the number of people that can take the cable car to the top of the mountain.\n",
    "choices": [
      "limit",
      "container",
      "presence",
      "restraint"
    ],
    "answer": "limit"
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ the search committee offers Doctor Rao the position of Professor of Sociology will depend on a vote of its members.\n",
    "choices": [
      "Whether",
      "After",
      "Although",
      "Until"
    ],
    "answer": "Whether"
  },
  {
    "question": "It is widely believed by medical practitioners that a nutritious, well-balanced diet increases energy and _________.\n",
    "choices": [
      "alert",
      "alerts",
      "alerted",
      "alertness"
    ],
    "answer": "alertness"
  },
  {
    "question": "Management believes that stagnant sales of the Pondhooper luggage line is result of the _________ advertising campaign that was launched last quarter.\n",
    "choices": [
      "inadequate",
      "rare",
      "intended",
      "trained"
    ],
    "answer": "inadequate"
  },
  {
    "question": "The number of visitors to the Hannaford Museum of History has _________ to exceed the goal set for this year.\n",
    "choices": [
      "often",
      "always",
      "yet",
      "sometimes"
    ],
    "answer": "yet"
  },
  {
    "question": "The MNS Railroad's most _________ passenger route runs through the White Mountain region and the Still River valley.\n",
    "choices": [
      "picture",
      "pictures",
      "picturing",
      "picturesque"
    ],
    "answer": "picturesque"
  },
  {
    "question": "The store _________ charged Ms. Han's credit card twice for the same purchase but quickly corrected its error.\n",
    "choices": [
      "uniformly",
      "potentially",
      "inadvertently",
      "functionally"
    ],
    "answer": "inadvertently"
  },
  {
    "question": "Due to a rise in revenue, the Easthampton town council has decided to increase _________ for community programs that have not traditionally received much financial support.\n",
    "choices": [
      "preservation",
      "sharing",
      "appraisal",
      "funding"
    ],
    "answer": "funding"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tara Kwon will _________ the results of the cafeteria survey via e-mail.\n",
    "choices": [
      "share",
      "shares",
      "sharing",
      "shared"
    ],
    "answer": "share"
  },
  {
    "question": "The sales department can take Friday off _________ the team worked overtime last weekend.\n",
    "choices": [
      "next",
      "because",
      "past",
      "again"
    ],
    "answer": "because"
  },
  {
    "question": "Salinas Floral Company is working _________ Hakui Studios to create a new logo.\n",
    "choices": [
      "along",
      "between",
      "with",
      "out"
    ],
    "answer": "with"
  },
  {
    "question": "Conference attendees must wear _________ name badges throughout the day.\n",
    "choices": [
      "them",
      "their",
      "they",
      "theirs"
    ],
    "answer": "their"
  },
  {
    "question": "The new CEO of Katori Housewares Ltd. has expressed a strong _________ in opening a store in Singapore.\n",
    "choices": [
      "interest",
      "progress",
      "worth",
      "output"
    ],
    "answer": "interest"
  },
  {
    "question": "Please read the following guidelines for _________ books to the Hartleton Public Library.\n",
    "choices": [
      "donate",
      "donates",
      "to donate",
      "donating"
    ],
    "answer": "donating"
  },
  {
    "question": "Zellacor Software, Inc., _________ hires part-time programmers and information technology specialists.\n",
    "choices": [
      "closely",
      "highly",
      "nearly",
      "frequently"
    ],
    "answer": "frequently"
  },
  {
    "question": "Legal documents due at the main office by 5:00 P.M. must be given to the courier _________ noon.\n",
    "choices": [
      "or",
      "before",
      "since",
      "now"
    ],
    "answer": "before"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ms. Kanno is scheduled _________ from her vacation next week.\n",
    "choices": [
      "returning",
      "returns",
      "returned",
      "to return"
    ],
    "answer": "to return"
  },
  {
    "question": "Taking courses at the Bedford Business Center can lead to greater opportunities for professional _________.\n",
    "choices": [
      "grown",
      "grow",
      "grows",
      "growth"
    ],
    "answer": "growth"
  },
  {
    "question": "Starchitect Il is _________ to be another best-selling video game from Stellar Play Studio.\n",
    "choices": [
      "popular",
      "expected",
      "successful",
      "enjoyed"
    ],
    "answer": "expected"
  },
  {
    "question": "Orders placed on Morgan Clothing's online site _________ arrive within five business days.\n",
    "choices": [
      "normal",
      "normalcy",
      "norm",
      "normally"
    ],
    "answer": "normally"
  },
  {
    "question": "Keola Resorts in Hawaii offer _________ weekly and monthly rental options.\n",
    "choices": [
      "both",
      "either",
      "when",
      "despite"
    ],
    "answer": "both"
  },
  {
    "question": "Many dishes served at the Urban Café contain vegetables harvested by Chef DuFour _________.\n",
    "choices": [
      "him",
      "his",
      "himself",
      "he"
    ],
    "answer": "himself"
  },
  {
    "question": "Kelang Manufacturing's decision to _________ in new machinery resulted in a 20 percent increase in production.\n",
    "choices": [
      "buy",
      "place",
      "invest",
      "charge"
    ],
    "answer": "invest"
  },
  {
    "question": "To meet the audit deadline, accountants at Lyang Associates must submit all financial reports by tomorrow morning at the _________.\n",
    "choices": [
      "latest",
      "lowest",
      "oldest",
      "finest"
    ],
    "answer": "latest"
  },
  {
    "question": "Artrox Photogranhy carries just-released products, along with _________ used equipment.\n",
    "choices": [
      "lighten",
      "lightly",
      "light",
      "lightened"
    ],
    "answer": "lightly"
  },
  {
    "question": "Rechargeable batteries today _________ almost twice as long as those produced ten years ago.\n",
    "choices": [
      "last",
      "lasts",
      "lasting",
      "lastly"
    ],
    "answer": "last"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tafani Motors' fuel-efficient utility vehicles _________ achieve between 9 and 13 kilometers per liter.\n",
    "choices": [
      "exactly",
      "typically",
      "sharply",
      "heavily"
    ],
    "answer": "typically"
  },
  {
    "question": "The expansion of Grantley Furniture's warehouse will provide additional _________ for its sizable line of merchandise.\n",
    "choices": [
      "store",
      "stored",
      "storage",
      "storable"
    ],
    "answer": "storage"
  },
  {
    "question": "Creative Director Ray Rabelo's unique ideas have been _________ to our reputation as a leading design firm.\n",
    "choices": [
      "main",
      "former",
      "average",
      "central"
    ],
    "answer": "central"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Keltes Corporation is one of the largest _________ of electronic supplies in the region.\n",
    "choices": [
      "provide",
      "providing",
      "providers",
      "provider"
    ],
    "answer": "providers"
  },
  {
    "question": "To ensure that a Web site is effective, it is common _________ to administer a customer feedback survey.\n",
    "choices": [
      "source",
      "practice",
      "topic",
      "supply"
    ],
    "answer": "practice"
  },
  {
    "question": "Each drawer in a Klein-Dock file cabinet can hold _________ one thousand sheets of letter-sized paper.\n",
    "choices": [
      "up to",
      "away from",
      "in place of",
      "in addition to"
    ],
    "answer": "up to"
  },
  {
    "question": "After talk show host Oliver Russo's weekly celebrity interview, MRM Radio posts a _________ of the broadcast on the station's Web site.\n",
    "choices": [
      "transcribe",
      "transcriber",
      "transcription",
      "transcripts"
    ],
    "answer": "transcription"
  },
  {
    "question": "When Gadget Guide Weekly tested the laptops introduced this year, the star 1000 was rated the _________.\n",
    "choices": [
      "powerful",
      "powerfully",
      "more powerful",
      "most powerful"
    ],
    "answer": "most powerful"
  },
  {
    "question": "Zoe O'Heir's novel Hanalei Sunset experienced such success _________ six months of its release that it was subsequently translated into five different languages.\n",
    "choices": [
      "for",
      "about",
      "beneath",
      "within"
    ],
    "answer": "within"
  },
  {
    "question": "At Ortega Agricultural Consulting, we look beyond _________ farming techniques to find innovative solutions for our clients.\n",
    "choices": [
      "convention",
      "conventional",
      "conventionally",
      "conventions"
    ],
    "answer": "conventional"
  },
  {
    "question": "Dr. Charles Lim, a renowned biologist, has written _________ about marine life in the Gulf of Mexico.\n",
    "choices": [
      "extent",
      "extensive",
      "extensively",
      "extensiveness"
    ],
    "answer": "extensively"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Soseu Soan Cornoration lunched an advertisina campaian to _________ interest in its new line of cleanina products.\n",
    "choices": [
      "consume",
      "generate",
      "endorse",
      "suppose"
    ],
    "answer": "generate"
  },
  {
    "question": "As the grant application for additional funding cannot exceed five pages, all research must be presented thoroughly yet _________.\n",
    "choices": [
      "concisely",
      "excessively",
      "evidently",
      "actually"
    ],
    "answer": "concisely"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mr. Nahm has been promoted to Senior Vice President of Sales and _________ his new role on March 1.\n",
    "choices": [
      "remains",
      "concerns",
      "assumes",
      "participates"
    ],
    "answer": "assumes"
  },
  {
    "question": "As soon as the automatic bottling machine is installed, the packaging _________ of the production process should be more efficient.\n",
    "choices": [
      "phase",
      "decision",
      "industry",
      "occasion"
    ],
    "answer": "phase"
  },
  {
    "question": "This year's Middletown Poetry Prize will be awarded to Mie Hasegawa, _________ poem Venus was selected from over 500 entries.\n",
    "choices": [
      "which",
      "whom",
      "whose",
      "what"
    ],
    "answer": "whose"
  },
  {
    "question": "Dr. Park's recent article further helped to _________ the research available on changing sleep patterns.\n",
    "choices": [
      "subside",
      "itemize",
      "clarify",
      "intend"
    ],
    "answer": "clarify"
  },
  {
    "question": "It is Calcor Furnishings' policy to issue payment to its textile suppliers _________ the shipments have been inspected.\n",
    "choices": [
      "once",
      "until",
      "thus",
      "due to"
    ],
    "answer": "once"
  },
  {
    "question": "Confidential reports regarding product innovation should not be shared with anyone _________ the company.\n",
    "choices": [
      "combined with",
      "outside",
      "upon",
      "unlike"
    ],
    "answer": "outside"
  },
  {
    "question": "Grantor Automotive, Inc., is designing a series of specialized tires that will be more _________ to punctures than standard tires.\n",
    "choices": [
      "resistant",
      "cautious",
      "specific",
      "consistent"
    ],
    "answer": "resistant"
  },
  {
    "question": "The opening of new markets in Ghana was cited as an _________ outcome of the business merger.\n",
    "choices": [
      "anticipates",
      "anticipation",
      "anticipating",
      "anticipated"
    ],
    "answer": "anticipated"
  },
  {
    "question": "The plan to renovate the water-treatment facility in Nanjing will _________ short-term costs but will guarantee valuable long-term benefits.\n",
    "choices": [
      "impose",
      "burden",
      "exchange",
      "persuade"
    ],
    "answer": "impose"
  },
  {
    "question": "The confirmation e-mail will contain both a tracking number _________ an approximate delivery date.\n",
    "choices": [
      "or",
      "as",
      "but",
      "and"
    ],
    "answer": "and"
  },
  {
    "question": "While he is away from the office, we can reach Mr. Cho by calling _________ home phone number.\n",
    "choices": [
      "himself",
      "him",
      "he",
      "his"
    ],
    "answer": "his"
  },
  {
    "question": "You may note any special meal requests _________ the space provided on the enclosed form.\n",
    "choices": [
      "up",
      "out",
      "in",
      "of"
    ],
    "answer": "in"
  },
  {
    "question": "Fabrics from Harmia Textiles are known for their vibrant _________.\n",
    "choices": [
      "colors",
      "colored",
      "colorful",
      "colorfully"
    ],
    "answer": "colors"
  },
  {
    "question": "Jemline Electronics is _________ daily from 9 A.M. to 7 P.M.\n",
    "choices": [
      "broad",
      "open",
      "whole",
      "frequent"
    ],
    "answer": "open"
  },
  {
    "question": "Recently, Jongno Art Museum has produced several _________ praised award-winning exhibitions.\n",
    "choices": [
      "height",
      "highest",
      "highly",
      "high"
    ],
    "answer": "highly"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Riverio Sporting Goods Web site will first appear sometime _________ January 1.\n",
    "choices": [
      "after",
      "without",
      "among",
      "behind"
    ],
    "answer": "after"
  },
  {
    "question": "Because of roadwork, Ms. Neeley's drive to the office may _________ longer than usual.\n",
    "choices": [
      "move",
      "take",
      "act",
      "do"
    ],
    "answer": "take"
  },
  {
    "question": "All _________ must wear protective headgear in work areas.\n",
    "choices": [
      "employer",
      "employee",
      "employees",
      "employing"
    ],
    "answer": "employees"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Hirota Computer Store is _________ located on Shijo Street in downtown Kyoto.\n",
    "choices": [
      "center",
      "centers",
      "centralize",
      "centrally"
    ],
    "answer": "centrally"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tedeschi Shoes _________ a discount to students of Brinkley University.\n",
    "choices": [
      "seems",
      "pleases",
      "meets",
      "offers"
    ],
    "answer": "offers"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mr. Shah's keynote speech will be followed _________ a banquet in the dining hall.\n",
    "choices": [
      "on",
      "amid",
      "by",
      "onto"
    ],
    "answer": "by"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Yuja Deluxe Grill must be cleaned _________ in order to function well.\n",
    "choices": [
      "regular",
      "regularly",
      "regularity",
      "regularize"
    ],
    "answer": "regularly"
  },
  {
    "question": "Most survey participants had _________ opinions about Virtanen's new line of hair care products.\n",
    "choices": [
      "positivity",
      "positive",
      "positives",
      "positively"
    ],
    "answer": "positive"
  },
  {
    "question": "Once you have placed your _________, its status will be available on our Web site.\n",
    "choices": [
      "order",
      "value",
      "refund",
      "sale"
    ],
    "answer": "order"
  },
  {
    "question": "Festival attendees should reserve a hotel room _________ in advance of their arrival next month.\n",
    "choices": [
      "well",
      "So",
      "such",
      "over"
    ],
    "answer": "well"
  },
  {
    "question": "Although pay is _________ distributed in the form of electronic bank deposits, staff may request that a check be issued instead.\n",
    "choices": [
      "generalize",
      "generalization",
      "generally",
      "general"
    ],
    "answer": "generally"
  },
  {
    "question": "According to Murata-Abe's corporate _________, each team member receives an annual performance review.\n",
    "choices": [
      "supply",
      "degree",
      "worth",
      "policy"
    ],
    "answer": "policy"
  },
  {
    "question": "The winter publication schedule has _________ been distributed to the editors.\n",
    "choices": [
      "already",
      "when",
      "tomorrow",
      "ever"
    ],
    "answer": "already"
  },
  {
    "question": "Meath Cosmetics sales representatives will receive a €400 bonus, _________ they did last year.\n",
    "choices": [
      "in spite of",
      "just as",
      "to which",
      "in order to"
    ],
    "answer": "just as"
  },
  {
    "question": "I look forward to hearing from you as soon as you _________ from your vacation.\n",
    "choices": [
      "had returned",
      "return",
      "returned",
      "will return"
    ],
    "answer": "return"
  },
  {
    "question": "The cancellation of Saturday's concert at Madison Hall was _________ unexpected problems with the sound system.\n",
    "choices": [
      "because",
      "as if",
      "due to",
      "unless"
    ],
    "answer": "due to"
  },
  {
    "question": "Zogu Industries _________ inspects each stage of its manufacturing process to ensure the highest-quality products.\n",
    "choices": [
      "closely",
      "closer",
      "closest",
      "closeness"
    ],
    "answer": "closely"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Buramsan Polar Star refrigerator is _________, requiring less energy than similar appliances.\n",
    "choices": [
      "transferable",
      "considerable",
      "absorbent",
      "efficient"
    ],
    "answer": "efficient"
  },
  {
    "question": "Local artists sell their handmade _________ at the Canbury Market every Saturday morning.\n",
    "choices": [
      "creative",
      "creations",
      "created",
      "creatively"
    ],
    "answer": "creations"
  },
  {
    "question": "Berne Tech has recommended that its clients _________ the invoices from tho last quarter for pricing irregularities.\n",
    "choices": [
      "to review",
      "reviewed",
      "review",
      "reviewing"
    ],
    "answer": "review"
  },
  {
    "question": "User response to Sandling's online publishing service has been largely _________, with only a handful of unsatisfactory ratings.\n",
    "choices": [
      "enthusiastic",
      "talented",
      "perpetual",
      "comfortable"
    ],
    "answer": "enthusiastic"
  },
  {
    "question": "If a customer finds the product advertised _________ for less, we will gladly match the lower price.\n",
    "choices": [
      "together",
      "elsewhere",
      "beside",
      "mutually"
    ],
    "answer": "elsewhere"
  },
  {
    "question": "Cars from Lefebre Motors come with a warranty lasting 36 months or 60,000 kilometers, _________ comes first.\n",
    "choices": [
      "whichever",
      "either",
      "each other",
      "whoever"
    ],
    "answer": "whichever"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you believe you have received this e-mail alert _________, please contact your customer service representative immediately.\n",
    "choices": [
      "at odds",
      "on demand",
      "upon request",
      "in error"
    ],
    "answer": "in error"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the event of _________ weather, the employee recognition ceremony will be relocated from the gardens to the conference room.\n",
    "choices": [
      "vigilant",
      "unfounded",
      "susceptible",
      "inclement"
    ],
    "answer": "inclement"
  },
  {
    "question": "Although Brawley Manufacturing is struggling domestically, its international ventures have become _________.\n",
    "choices": [
      "success",
      "more successful",
      "successfulness",
      "most successfully"
    ],
    "answer": "more successful"
  },
  {
    "question": "While no one has called for an _________ end to hiring temporary workers, the human resources department has begun to recruit additional permanent staff.\n",
    "choices": [
      "apart",
      "alike",
      "indeed",
      "outright"
    ],
    "answer": "outright"
  },
  {
    "question": "Jean Perets has been singled out as the ideal choice _________ Azoulay Pharmaceuticals once CEO Raviv Dayag retires in December.\n",
    "choices": [
      "will lead",
      "to have led",
      "to lead",
      "having led"
    ],
    "answer": "to lead"
  },
  {
    "question": "Warehouse personnel should report to work as usual _________ otherwise directed by their supervisors.\n",
    "choices": [
      "nonetheless",
      "except that",
      "if not",
      "at least as"
    ],
    "answer": "if not"
  },
  {
    "question": "The mist-covered mountains and forests of Merlet Island provide an ideal _________ for your vacation photographs.\n",
    "choices": [
      "outcast",
      "difference",
      "reception",
      "backdrop"
    ],
    "answer": "backdrop"
  },
  {
    "question": "Gormley and Company owns several subsidiaries in Asia that have divided _________ into smaller entities to focus on specialized services.\n",
    "choices": [
      "theirs",
      "themselves",
      "its",
      "itself"
    ],
    "answer": "themselves"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Felton factory conducts testing of its equipment only _________ government regulations stipulate.\n",
    "choices": [
      "insofar as",
      "in order that",
      "in consequence of",
      "in accordance with"
    ],
    "answer": "insofar as"
  },
  {
    "question": "By signing this form, I agree to _________ to the revised protocol for client confidentiality.\n",
    "choices": [
      "convene",
      "remain",
      "adhere",
      "divulge"
    ],
    "answer": "adhere"
  },
  {
    "question": "Caley-Hibernia management asks that cameras and mobile phones _________ at the security desk before the tour of the facility commences.\n",
    "choices": [
      "left",
      "were left",
      "will be leaving",
      "be left"
    ],
    "answer": "be left"
  },
  {
    "question": "Gerardo Lentini will build _________ second clinic in June.\n",
    "choices": [
      "he",
      "his",
      "him",
      "himself"
    ],
    "answer": "his"
  },
  {
    "question": "The manufacturer recommends cleaning the natural wood table with a _________ cotton cloth.\n",
    "choices": [
      "dry",
      "dryly",
      "dryness",
      "to dry"
    ],
    "answer": "dry"
  },
  {
    "question": "If _________ are willing to work on the project this weekend, Ms. Craig will buy everyone lunch.\n",
    "choices": [
      "employees",
      "employing",
      "employments",
      "employs"
    ],
    "answer": "employees"
  },
  {
    "question": "Analysts _________ significant growth in the robotics industry in the next decade.\n",
    "choices": [
      "attend",
      "refer",
      "think",
      "predict"
    ],
    "answer": "predict"
  },
  {
    "question": "Please review the _________ schedule and e-mail me right away about any mistakes.\n",
    "choices": [
      "repeated",
      "alarmed",
      "attached",
      "canceled"
    ],
    "answer": "attached"
  },
  {
    "question": "Niceties Cake Shop added ten more exotic flavors _________ after opening.\n",
    "choices": [
      "short",
      "shortest",
      "shorter",
      "shortly"
    ],
    "answer": "shortly"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mr. Kern has built a shelf in the supply closet _________ all the new materials.\n",
    "choices": [
      "accommodate",
      "accommodates",
      "to accommodate",
      "is accommodating"
    ],
    "answer": "to accommodate"
  },
  {
    "question": "The neighborhood's newest clothing store will specialize in the sale of _________ wear.\n",
    "choices": [
      "formal",
      "quick",
      "strict",
      "sudden"
    ],
    "answer": "formal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Office morale _________ after we offered rewards for practical suggestions.\n",
    "choices": [
      "indicated",
      "completed",
      "improved",
      "controlled"
    ],
    "answer": "improved"
  },
  {
    "question": "At Furred Finance, _________ encourage associates with different points of view to find common ground.\n",
    "choices": [
      "ourselves",
      "ours",
      "us",
      "we"
    ],
    "answer": "we"
  },
  {
    "question": "Shipbuilders, Inc., anticipates profits for the second quarter to be _________ 4 and 6 percent.\n",
    "choices": [
      "by",
      "for",
      "upon",
      "between"
    ],
    "answer": "between"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ovonel Skincare has published _________ testimonials on several social media sites.\n",
    "choices": [
      "consumed",
      "consumer",
      "consume",
      "consuming"
    ],
    "answer": "consumer"
  },
  {
    "question": "Saturn Bank is working _________ to resolve technical difficulties with its mobile app and online banking.\n",
    "choices": [
      "quickening",
      "quickened",
      "quickness",
      "quickly"
    ],
    "answer": "quickly"
  },
  {
    "question": "The new washing machine has a heavy-duty cycle that is effective in removing the _________ stains.\n",
    "choices": [
      "highest",
      "toughest",
      "uneven",
      "broad"
    ],
    "answer": "toughest"
  },
  {
    "question": "Wolff Foods has recently experienced a decrease in _________ for its beef products.\n",
    "choices": [
      "position",
      "approach",
      "force",
      "demand"
    ],
    "answer": "demand"
  },
  {
    "question": "Although construction will begin on Reese-Decker Bridge tomorrow, it should cause _________ traffic problems.\n",
    "choices": [
      "minimal",
      "minimally",
      "minimum",
      "minimize"
    ],
    "answer": "minimal"
  },
  {
    "question": "The months of April and May are _________ busy for the workers at Avedis Garden Supply.\n",
    "choices": [
      "readily",
      "accurately",
      "particularly",
      "directly"
    ],
    "answer": "particularly"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mr. Kalama will handle the marketing reports _________ Ms. Lewis is away on vacation.\n",
    "choices": [
      "concerning",
      "while",
      "during",
      "just"
    ],
    "answer": "while"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mr. Nguyen opposes adding a _________ of trail bikes because he thinks it will not be popular with customers.\n",
    "choices": [
      "line",
      "surface",
      "field",
      "front"
    ],
    "answer": "line"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ms. Nicholas was promoted _________ managing editor of the Irontown Daily Press.\n",
    "choices": [
      "of",
      "at",
      "to",
      "on"
    ],
    "answer": "to"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ms. Chou has ordered the _________ of all the bookcases sold by Bielke Office Furnishings.\n",
    "choices": [
      "narrowly",
      "narrower",
      "narrowest",
      "narrow"
    ],
    "answer": "narrowest"
  },
  {
    "question": "Failure to pay bills on time _________ result in additional late fees.\n",
    "choices": [
      "when",
      "may",
      "part",
      "itself"
    ],
    "answer": "may"
  },
  {
    "question": "Financial conditions in the greater Perth region are _________ favorable for economic growth.\n",
    "choices": [
      "privately",
      "centrally",
      "neutrally",
      "currently"
    ],
    "answer": "currently"
  },
  {
    "question": "The quarterly data safety report provides _________ for Mardoor Investing's strict security policies.\n",
    "choices": [
      "justify",
      "justifier",
      "justified",
      "justification"
    ],
    "answer": "justification"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sunworth Company's all-in-one shampoos restore natural shine at the same time _________ they condition hair.\n",
    "choices": [
      "even",
      "as",
      "either",
      "like"
    ],
    "answer": "as"
  },
  {
    "question": "The third box of the shipment, which should have contained the microphones, _________ arrived.\n",
    "choices": [
      "late",
      "rather",
      "never",
      "not"
    ],
    "answer": "never"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Murnau Company's pepper grinders are _________ durable that the company guarantees them for life.\n",
    "choices": [
      "too",
      "so",
      "such",
      "very"
    ],
    "answer": "so"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Asawa 4 is _________ any vehicle currently on the is market.\n",
    "choices": [
      "unlike",
      "excepting",
      "against",
      "above"
    ],
    "answer": "unlike"
  },
  {
    "question": "By the time he signs the lease, Mr. Cooper _________ four months searching for a suitable office space.\n",
    "choices": [
      "will have spent",
      "had spent",
      "to spend",
      "spent"
    ],
    "answer": "will have spent"
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ I have already been briefed by the product development team, I am fully prepared for my appointment with Mr. Warner.\n",
    "choices": [
      "Until",
      "In spite of",
      "Since",
      "Even though"
    ],
    "answer": "Since"
  },
  {
    "question": "It is advisable to assign new tasks _________ to interns during the first month of training.\n",
    "choices": [
      "slow",
      "slowest",
      "slowly",
      "slows"
    ],
    "answer": "slowly"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mr. Barton and his team provide services ranging _________ fund-raising to coordinating events.\n",
    "choices": [
      "like",
      "for",
      "from",
      "through"
    ],
    "answer": "from"
  },
  {
    "question": "Customers who sign up for Garrett Tea Company's mailing list will receive free shipping on _________ next online order.\n",
    "choices": [
      "theirs",
      "them",
      "their",
      "themselves"
    ],
    "answer": "their"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mr. Iwata likes to be prepared, so he _________ arrives fifteen minutes early to meetings.\n",
    "choices": [
      "very",
      "once",
      "quite",
      "always"
    ],
    "answer": "always"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ms. Fache is heading a committee that will explore ways to make the province more _________ for small businesses.\n",
    "choices": [
      "afford",
      "affording",
      "affordable",
      "afforded"
    ],
    "answer": "affordable"
  },  
  {
    "question": "The repair estimate _________ all costs for labor parts.\n",
    "choices": [
      "prefers",
      "accepts",
      "includes",
      "surrounds"
    ],
    "answer": "includes"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Destven Institute contact is a key _________ of information on energy-related matters.\n",
    "choices": [
      "sourced",
      "source",
      "sources",
      "sourcing"
    ],
    "answer": "source"
  }, 
  {
    "question": "East Highlands Adventures now offers guided hikes along several trails that the state _________ opened.\n",
    "choices": [
      "especially",
      "rigidly",
      "recently",
      "intensely"
    ],
    "answer": "recently"
  }, 
  {
    "question": "Customer complaints that cannot be resolved _________ a call-center representative should be referred to a supervisor.\n",
    "choices": [
      "out",
      "by",
      "and",
      "or"
    ],
    "answer": "by"
  }, 
  {
    "question": "_________ filling out the online form, applicants must also upload a résumé.\n",
    "choices": [
      "Furthermore",
      "Except for",
      "As far as",
      "In addition to"
    ],
    "answer": "In addition to"
  }, 
  {
    "question": "Allentown Paint Supply relocated _________ downtown office to Trenton Street.\n",
    "choices": [
      "they",
      "ours",
      "yours",
      "its"
    ],
    "answer": "its"
  }, 
  {
    "question": "The merchandise will be placed in a storage facility _________ the warehouse roof repairs are completed.\n",
    "choices": [
      "over",
      "past",
      "with",
      "until"
    ],
    "answer": "until"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Hartsfield Hotel offers _________ contemporary comforts for a building that was constructed a century ago.\n",
    "choices": [
      "impressive",
      "impression",
      "impressed",
      "to impress"
    ],
    "answer": "impressive"
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ Mr. Assink placed the order early, it still arrived late.\n",
    "choices": [
      "Equally",
      "Besides",
      "Although",
      "Likewise"
    ],
    "answer": "Although"
  },
  {
    "question": "Due to the lack of _________, the president of Murtha Industries was not informed of the employees' concerns.\n",
    "choices": [
      "communicate",
      "communicative",
      "communicated",
      "communication"
    ],
    "answer": "communication"
  },
  {
    "question": "The board of directors came to the _________ that it was necessary to hire a new CEO.\n",
    "choices": [
      "conclusion",
      "distinction",
      "requirement",
      "statement"
    ],
    "answer": "conclusion"
  },
  {
    "question": "Claudine Dumay has been Neelon's head of purchasing _________ it opened for business.\n",
    "choices": [
      "ever",
      "before",
      "since",
      "nonetheless"
    ],
    "answer": "since"
  },
  {
    "question": "Amaford Stationery Store customers are asked to _________ a customer satisfaction survey after shopping.\n",
    "choices": [
      "delegate",
      "rehearse",
      "accompany",
      "complete"
    ],
    "answer": "complete"
  },
  {
    "question": "Argorot Ltd. is working to create a steady supply chain _________ many challenges.\n",
    "choices": [
      "former",
      "despite",
      "about",
      "otherwise"
    ],
    "answer": "despite"
  },
  {
    "question": "The director of North Ridge Library states that giving young children easy _________ to books promotes a love of reading.\n",
    "choices": [
      "access",
      "path",
      "key",
      "way"
    ],
    "answer": "access"
  },
  {
    "question": "The city council president said that getting the road-improvement bill passed was a significant _________.\n",
    "choices": [
      "achieve",
      "achieves",
      "achieving",
      "achievement"
    ],
    "answer": "achievement"
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ the memo, attendance at tomorrow's seminar is mandatory.\n",
    "choices": [
      "According to",
      "Ahead of",
      "Along with",
      "Away from"
    ],
    "answer": "According to"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mr. Park _________ missed his flight because of the severe traffic congestion this morning.\n",
    "choices": [
      "near",
      "nearly",
      "nearing",
      "nearest"
    ],
    "answer": "nearly"
  },
  {
    "question": "_________ breakfast is served daily for our club members from 6:00 A.M. to 9:30 A.M.\n",
    "choices": [
      "Complimentary",
      "Appreciative",
      "Favorable",
      "Courteous"
    ],
    "answer": "Complimentary"
  },
  {
    "question": "The study looks at major competitors in the marketplace and how they _________ themselves.\n",
    "choices": [
      "different",
      "difference",
      "differently",
      "differentiate"
    ],
    "answer": "differentiate"
  },
  {
    "question": "Because Mr. Takata will be at the trade show, other marketing team members will _________ be there as well.\n",
    "choices": [
      "sharply",
      "longer",
      "probably",
      "almost"
    ],
    "answer": "probably"
  },
  {
    "question": "Inxspace Corporation is the region's largest company, employing _________ 4,000 people.\n",
    "choices": [
      "approximately",
      "approximate",
      "approximation",
      "approximated"
    ],
    "answer": "approximately"
  },
  {
    "question": "Rojo Kitchen Products is following its _________ expansion plans by purchasing the Vernick Square Group.\n",
    "choices": [
      "retired",
      "ambitious",
      "hesitant",
      "automatic"
    ],
    "answer": "ambitious"
  },
  {
    "question": "Horsham Engineering's accountant Kae Jung-Ho _________ the average yearly cost of company operations.\n",
    "choices": [
      "determine",
      "determined",
      "determining",
      "determination"
    ],
    "answer": "determined"
  },
  {
    "question": "Making digital copies of files is a smart way to deal with an _________ of important documents.\n",
    "choices": [
      "abundance",
      "extension",
      "accordance",
      "instance"
    ],
    "answer": "abundance"
  }
]